Yoo N.; Russakovsky O.,Efficient  Self-Supervised Human Pose Estimation with Inductive Prior Tuning,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952325&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00351&partnerID=40&md5=d3ece63958d170c0f2b54d818de2b35d,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Princeton University  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Princeton University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Rao A.; Lee J.-Y.; Aalami O.,Studying the Impact of Augmentations on Medical Confidence Calibration,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952321&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00260&partnerID=40&md5=98be509a3d1fb3317d3e70cb92be0e72,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Stanford University  United States; Palo Alto High School  United States; Adobe Research  United States,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Stanford University""  ""Palo Alto High School""  ""Adobe Research""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [""Palo Alto""] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Havtorn J.D.; Royer A.; Blankevoort T.; Bejnordi B.E.,MSViT: Dynamic Mixed-scale Tokenization for Vision Transformers,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182950022&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00091&partnerID=40&md5=bfaeee5b0f6ad9947713609466f7ad74,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Technical University of Denmark  Copenhagen  Denmark; Corti.ai  Copenhagen  Denmark; Qualcomm Ai Research  Amsterdam  Netherlands,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Technical University of Denmark"" 
    ""Corti.ai"" 
    ""Qualcomm Ai Research""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Copenhagen"" 
    ""Amsterdam""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Denmark"" 
    ""Denmark"" 
    ""Netherlands""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Singh P.; Chen L.; Chen M.; Pan J.; Chukkapalli R.; Chaudhari S.; Cirrone J.,Enhancing Medical Image Segmentation: Optimizing Cross-Entropy Weights and Post-Processing with Autoencoders,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946204&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00283&partnerID=40&md5=0907bb98631c248f1150d738c9beec49,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,New York University  Tandon School of Engineering  United States; New York University  Center for Data Science  United States; New York University  Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""New York University"" 
    ""Tandon School of Engineering"" 
    ""Center for Data Science"" 
    ""Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""New York""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Celikkan E.; Saberioon M.; Herold M.; Klein N.,Semantic Segmentation of Crops and Weeds with Probabilistic Modeling and Uncertainty Quantification,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946328&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00065&partnerID=40&md5=0076c34f9e1b98ced878a03513004216,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Gfz German Research Centre for Geosciences  Potsdam  Germany; Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin  Berlin  Germany; Technische Universität Dortmund  Research Center Trustworthy Data Science and Security  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Gfz German Research Centre for Geosciences"" 
    ""Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin"" 
    ""Technische Universität Dortmund"" 
    ""Research Center Trustworthy Data Science and Security""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Potsdam"" 
    ""Berlin""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Germany"" 
    ""Germany"" 
    ""Germany""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Wang Z.; Ma C.,Dual-Contrastive Dual-Consistency Dual-Transformer: A Semi-Supervised Approach to Medical Image Segmentation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182944429&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00094&partnerID=40&md5=f8a76d75eb3ed9bd5711f419ecf22984,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Oxford  Department of Computer Science  United Kingdom; University of Bath  Department of Computer Science  United Kingdom,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of Oxford"" 
    ""Department of Computer Science"" 
    ""University of Bath"" 
    ""Department of Computer Science""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Kingdom""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Ahmad M.; Park G.; Park D.; Park S.,MMTF: Multi-Modal Temporal Fusion for Commonsense Video Question Answering,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182949954&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00502&partnerID=40&md5=a29d37133c844878ee4afafa5c3bd6ea,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Pyler CO.  Ltd  Seoul  South Korea,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": ""Pyler CO.  Ltd"" 
  ""LOCATION"": ""Seoul"" 
  ""COUNTRY"": ""South Korea""
}"
Van Holland L.; Stotko P.; Krumpen S.; Klein R.; Weinmann M.,Efficient 3D Reconstruction  Streaming and Visualization of Static and Dynamic Scene Parts for Multi-client Live-telepresence in Large-scale Environments,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948986&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00460&partnerID=40&md5=d0d732946942df200a89b82dfba5e8af,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Bonn  Germany; Delft University of Technology  Netherlands,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of Bonn"" 
    ""Delft University of Technology""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Germany"" 
    ""Netherlands""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Cioni D.; Berlincioni L.; Becattini F.; Del Bimbo A.,Diffusion Based Augmentation for Captioning and Retrieval in Cultural Heritage,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945993&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00186&partnerID=40&md5=830e2cecc623e0a00e30fe6f98e22587,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Florence  Micc  Italy; University of Siena  Italy,-1,"```json
{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""University of Florence"" 
        ""Micc"" 
        ""University of Siena""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Italy""
    ]
}
```"
Rumberger J.L.; Franzen J.; Hirsch P.; Albrecht J.-P.; Kainmueller D.,ACTIS: Improving data efficiency by leveraging semi-supervised Augmentation Consistency Training for Instance Segmentation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182950493&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00410&partnerID=40&md5=1242427aeb8379f94e4ae61cb0cd09e4,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Max-Delbrück-Center for Molecular Medicine in the Helmholtz Association  Berlin  Germany; Charité University Medicine  Berlin  Germany; Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin  Faculty of Mathematics and Natural Sciences  Berlin  Germany; Potsdam University  Digital Engineering Faculty  Germany; Helmholtz Imaging  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Max-Delbrück-Center for Molecular Medicine"" 
    ""Helmholtz Association"" 
    ""Charité University Medicine"" 
    ""Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin"" 
    ""Faculty of Mathematics and Natural Sciences"" 
    ""Potsdam University"" 
    ""Digital Engineering Faculty"" 
    ""Helmholtz Imaging""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Berlin"" 
    ""Potsdam""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Germany""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Kumar Reddy N.K.; Killedar V.; Seelamantula C.S.,Quantized Generative Models for Solving Inverse Problems,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952038&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00167&partnerID=40&md5=3428cd5c8264da1c6b2e2ae2e34d4092,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Indian Institute of Science  Department of Electrical Engineering  Bengaluru  560012  India,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Indian Institute of Science""  ""Department of Electrical Engineering""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Bengaluru""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""India""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""560012""]
}"
Daroya R.; Sun A.; Maji S.,COSE: A Consistency-Sensitivity Metric for Saliency on Image Classification,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182953887&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00022&partnerID=40&md5=7188379148e39c57434be6918288563f,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Massachusetts Amherst  United States,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""University of Massachusetts Amherst""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Amherst""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""United States""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Jeong J.; Jeoun B.; Park Y.; Han B.,An Optimized Ensemble Framework for Multi-Label Classification on Long-Tailed Chest X-ray Data,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182953247&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00289&partnerID=40&md5=5bfa6b57b52657a2b425f13a6d0fa342,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Kt Corporation  Kt Research & Development Center  Seoul  South Korea; Seoul National University  Ece&ipai  Seoul  South Korea,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Kt Corporation"" 
        ""Kt Research & Development Center"" 
        ""Seoul National University"" 
        ""Ece&ipai""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Seoul""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""South Korea""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Arai T.; Iwata K.; Hara K.; Satoh Y.,Estimation of Human Condition at Disaster Site Using Aerial Drone Images,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182950134&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00408&partnerID=40&md5=184ebc861060f3c24710093013cf8f4e,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,National Institute of Advanced Industrial Science and Technology (AIST)  Information Technology and Human Factors  1-1-1 Umezono  Ibaraki  Tsukuba  305-8565  Japan; University of Tsukuba  Graduate School of Science and Technology  1-1-1 Tenoudai  Ibaraki  Tsukuba  305-8573  Japan,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""National Institute of Advanced Industrial Science and Technology (AIST)""  ""University of Tsukuba""  ""Graduate School of Science and Technology""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Ibaraki""  ""Tsukuba""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Japan""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""Information Technology and Human Factors""  ""1-1-1 Umezono""  ""1-1-1 Tenoudai""  ""305-8565""  ""305-8573""]
}"
Wang B.; Zhao K.; Zhao H.; Pu S.; Xiao B.; Guo J.,Video Attribute Prototype Network: A New Perspective for Zero-Shot Video Classification,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945105&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00039&partnerID=40&md5=bd531c868cddba7b350405e11ce6fd6e,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Beijing University of Posts and Telecommunications  China,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": ""Beijing University of Posts and Telecommunications"" 
    ""LOCATION"": ""Beijing"" 
    ""COUNTRY"": ""China""
}"
Xu C.; Tsuji S.; Makihara Y.; Li X.; Yagi Y.,Occluded Gait Recognition via Silhouette Registration Guided by Automated Occlusion Degree Estimation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948179&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00344&partnerID=40&md5=938e69437cb7e755621858adc9aea373,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Osaka University  Osaka  Japan,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": ""Osaka University"" 
  ""LOCATION"": ""Osaka"" 
  ""COUNTRY"": ""Japan""
}"
Garcia-Gasulla D.; Gimenez-Abalos V.; Martin-Torres P.,Padding Aware Neurons,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948451&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00017&partnerID=40&md5=29c4e3cc5ca657444442cf0cf6ecc9ca,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Universitat Politécnica de Catalunya - Barcelona Tech (UPC)  Spain; Barcelona Supercomputing Center (BSC)  Spain,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Universitat Politécnica de Catalunya - Barcelona Tech (UPC)"" 
    ""Barcelona Supercomputing Center (BSC)""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Barcelona""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Spain""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Park J.; Jung D.S.; Moon G.; Lee K.M.,Extract-and-Adaptation Network for 3D Interacting Hand Mesh Recovery,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945186&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00454&partnerID=40&md5=33a526877432969b120ce9135df91559,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Meta Reality Labs Research; Seoul National University  Dept. of Ece&asri  South Korea; Seoul National University  Ipai  South Korea; SNU-LG Ai Research Center  South Korea,-1,"{
	""ORGANIZATION"": [
		""Meta Reality Labs Research"" 
		""Seoul National University"" 
		""Dept. of Ece & asri"" 
		""SNU-LG Ai Research Center""
	] 
	""LOCATION"": [
		""Seoul""
	] 
	""COUNTRY"": [
		""South Korea""
	] 
	""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
		""Ipai""
	]
}"
Haurum J.B.; Escalera S.; Taylor G.W.; Moeslund T.B.,Which Tokens to Use? Investigating Token Reduction in Vision Transformers,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182949305&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00085&partnerID=40&md5=e508c374f76550b66112575884c12cca,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Universitat de Barcelona  Computer Vision Center  Spain; Aalborg University  Pioneer Centre for Ai  Visual Analysis and Perception (VAP) Laboratory  Denmark; University of Guelph  Vector Institute for Ai  Canada,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Universitat de Barcelona"" 
    ""Computer Vision Center"" 
    ""Aalborg University"" 
    ""Pioneer Centre for Ai"" 
    ""Visual Analysis and Perception (VAP) Laboratory"" 
    ""University of Guelph"" 
    ""Vector Institute for Ai""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Spain"" 
    ""Denmark"" 
    ""Canada""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Lv Z.; Han D.; Wang W.; Chen C.,IFPNet: Integrated Feature Pyramid Network with Fusion Factor for Lane Detection,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182953034&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00203&partnerID=40&md5=814377661d889caf2e96db222596db31,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Harbin Engineering University  China; Zhejiang University  China; Westlake University  China,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Harbin Engineering University""  ""Zhejiang University""  ""Westlake University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""China""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Sarhan N.; Frintrop S.,Unraveling a Decade: A Comprehensive Survey on Isolated Sign Language Recognition,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182947151&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00345&partnerID=40&md5=7947c670b0c81437c52b786cc4736410,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Universität Hamburg  Department of Informatics  Hamburg  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Universität Hamburg"" 
    ""Department of Informatics""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Hamburg""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Germany""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Li H.; Yi P.; Liu Y.; Zahor A.,Scalable MAV Indoor Reconstruction with Neural Implicit Surfaces,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952180&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00169&partnerID=40&md5=b7ecdad7318c82e78c2c04a3bc6d6f74,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of California  Berkeley  Berkeley  CA  United States,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""University of California  Berkeley""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Berkeley  CA""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""United States""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Haque M.; Chen S.; Haque W.; Liu C.; Yang W.,AntiNODE: Evaluating Efficiency Robustness of Neural ODEs,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948084&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00164&partnerID=40&md5=eb21b4c29b222ac19a3744eb6532b2d1,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Texas  Dallas  United States; Argo Data  United States; University of California  Riverside  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Texas""  ""Argo Data""  ""University of California  Riverside""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Dallas""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Engin D.; Avrithis Y.,Zero-Shot and Few-Shot Video Question Answering with Multi-Modal Prompts,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952468&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00298&partnerID=40&md5=3b94408b693700ba77b28c5b82f51bf6,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Univ Rennes  CNRS  IRISA  INRIA  France; Institute of Advanced Research in Artificial Intelligence (IARAI),-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Univ Rennes""  ""CNRS""  ""IRISA""  ""INRIA""  ""Institute of Advanced Research in Artificial Intelligence (IARAI)""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""France""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Ahmed M.; Lall B.; Kumar R.; Kherani A.A.,Towards estimation of human intent in assistive robotic teleoperation using kinaesthetic and visual feedback,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182951654&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00207&partnerID=40&md5=e1550240e071266e9d9efb9141ac3622,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Indian Institute of Technology Delhi  New Delhi  110016  India; Addverb Technologies  Noida  201310  India; Indian Institute of Technology Bhilai  Raipur  492015  India,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Indian Institute of Technology Delhi"" 
    ""Addverb Technologies"" 
    ""Indian Institute of Technology Bhilai""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""New Delhi"" 
    ""Noida"" 
    ""Raipur""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""India""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""110016"" 
    ""201310"" 
    ""492015""
  ]
}"
Oshima R.; Shinagawa S.; Tsunashima H.; Feng Q.; Morishima S.,Pointing out Human Answer Mistakes in a Goal-Oriented Visual Dialogue,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182950567&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00503&partnerID=40&md5=45f5cf233071cb610a6e6253c7d69b15,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Waseda University  Japan; Nara Institute of Science and Technology  Japan; Waseda Research Institute for Science and Engineering  Japan,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Waseda University"" 
        ""Nara Institute of Science and Technology"" 
        ""Waseda Research Institute for Science and Engineering""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Japan""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Thauvin D.; Herbin S.,Knowledge Informed Sequential Scene Graph Verification Using VQA,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182953313&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00009&partnerID=40&md5=cd30334d741b799b653995ca7677f249,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Université Paris Saclay  Onera  Dtis  Palaiseau  F-91123  France,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Université Paris Saclay""  ""Onera""  ""Dtis""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Palaiseau""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""France""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""F-91123""]
}"
Koch T.; Riess C.; Köhler T.,LORD: Leveraging Open-Set Recognition with Unknown Data,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182950200&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00473&partnerID=40&md5=617741edaee2780be2da3201d9061bcc,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,E.Solutions GmbH  Erlangen  Germany; Friedrich-Alexander-Universität Erlangen-Nürnberg  Erlangen  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""E.Solutions GmbH"" 
    ""Friedrich-Alexander-Universität Erlangen-Nürnberg""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Erlangen""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Germany""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Gula T.; Bertoldo J.P.C.,Gaussian Image Anomaly Detection with Greedy Eigencomponent Selection,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946226&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00444&partnerID=40&md5=d83d749e78a69986e6cfdddd9b6dbdc4,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Mines Paris  Psl University  Centre for Mathematical Morphology  Fontainebleau  77300  France,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Mines Paris""  ""Psl University""  ""Centre for Mathematical Morphology""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Fontainebleau""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""France""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""77300""]
}"
Lin C.-S.; Chen M.-H.; Wang Y.-C.F.,Frequency-Aware Self-Supervised Long-Tailed Learning,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952218&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00103&partnerID=40&md5=24a2e3ae48efafa9f7ee07cf4910bd74,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,National Taiwan University  Graduate Institute of Communication Engineering  Taiwan; Nvidia  Taiwan,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""National Taiwan University""  ""Graduate Institute of Communication Engineering""  ""Nvidia""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Taiwan""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Reich C.; Prangemeier T.; Koeppl H.,The TYC Dataset for Understanding Instance-Level Semantics and Motions of Cells in Microstructures,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182950832&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00426&partnerID=40&md5=fe9715bbb6c4e81fd8742eb7cba55ddc,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Technische Universität Darmstadt  Centre for Synthetic Biology  Department of Electrical Engineering and Information Technology  Germany,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Technische Universität Darmstadt""  ""Centre for Synthetic Biology""  ""Department of Electrical Engineering and Information Technology""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [""Darmstadt""] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""Germany""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Yoo J.-S.; Lee H.; Jung S.-W.,Hierarchical Spatiotemporal Transformers for Video Object Segmentation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952617&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00087&partnerID=40&md5=bd14c91bd41ec5e730285b966e0f8261,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Korea University  South Korea,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Korea University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""South Korea""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Noor N.; Park I.K.,A Lightweight Skeleton-Based 3D-CNN for Real-Time Fall Detection and Action Recognition,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182950439&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00232&partnerID=40&md5=81e816db1d7aacf2103add42759f39b1,1.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Inha University  Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering  Incheon  22212  South Korea,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Inha University"" 
        ""Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Incheon""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""South Korea""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
        ""22212""
    ]
}"
Tsuji M.; Fujimura Y.; Funatomi T.; Mukaigawa Y.; Morimoto T.; Oishi T.; Takamatsu J.; Ikeuchi K.,Pigment Mapping for Tomb Murals using Neural Representation and Physics-based Model,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182949298&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00182&partnerID=40&md5=7f0b09f43e8f03492e7cf54f57c52b41,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Nara Institute of Science and Technology  Japan; The University of Tokyo  Japan; Microsoft,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Nara Institute of Science and Technology""  ""The University of Tokyo""  ""Microsoft""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Japan""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Kumbar A.; Anvekar T.; Tabib R.A.; Mudenagudi U.,ASUR3D: Arbitrary Scale Upsampling and Refinement of 3D Point Clouds using Local Occupancy Fields,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182949177&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00180&partnerID=40&md5=979329d0da880992836014df8e62d297,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Kle Technological University  Center of Excellence in Visual Intelligence (CEVI)  Hubballi  Karnataka  Vidyanagar  India,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Kle Technological University""  ""Center of Excellence in Visual Intelligence (CEVI)""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Hubballi""  ""Vidyanagar""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""India""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""Karnataka""]
}"
Mondal A.; Nag S.; Prada J.M.; Zhu X.; Dutta A.,Actor-agnostic Multi-label Action Recognition with Multi-modal Query,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945495&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00086&partnerID=40&md5=b49fa9baf72bdf698ec34c1d9d8b055e,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Surrey  United Kingdom; Cvssp  United Kingdom; Surrey Institute for People-Centred Ai  United Kingdom; School of Veterinary Medicine  Tunisia; IFlyTek-Surrey Joint Research Center on Ai  United Kingdom,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of Surrey"" 
    ""Cvssp"" 
    ""Surrey Institute for People-Centred Ai"" 
    ""School of Veterinary Medicine"" 
    ""IFlyTek-Surrey Joint Research Center on Ai""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""United Kingdom"" 
    ""United Kingdom"" 
    ""United Kingdom"" 
    ""Tunisia"" 
    ""United Kingdom""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Kingdom"" 
    ""United Kingdom"" 
    ""United Kingdom"" 
    ""Tunisia"" 
    ""United Kingdom""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Venkataramanan A.; Benbihi A.; Laviale M.; Pradalier C.,Gaussian Latent Representations for Uncertainty Estimation using Mahalanobis Distance in Deep Classifiers,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182949458&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00483&partnerID=40&md5=22baa9492da71b9dcb4c33a94e57fbb7,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Université de Lorraine  CNRS  Liec  Metz  France; Georgia Tech Europe  GT-CNRS Irl  Metz  2958  France; LTSER-'Zone Atelier Moselle'  Metz  France; Czech Technical University  Czech Institute of Informatics  Robotics and Cybernetics  Prague  Czech Republic,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Université de Lorraine"" 
    ""CNRS"" 
    ""Liec"" 
    ""Georgia Tech Europe"" 
    ""GT-CNRS Irl"" 
    ""Czech Technical University"" 
    ""Czech Institute of Informatics  Robotics and Cybernetics""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Metz"" 
    ""Prague""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""France"" 
    ""France"" 
    ""France"" 
    ""Czech Republic""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""LTSER-'Zone Atelier Moselle'""
  ]
}"
De Avellar Sarmento A.H.; Antonelli Ponti M.,A Cross-Dataset Study on the Brazilian Sign Language Translation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948523&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00300&partnerID=40&md5=0bbd41f3f96e9c05d6b8448703637036,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Icmc  Universidade de São Paulo  SP  São Carlos  Brazil,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""ICMC"" 
    ""Universidade de São Paulo""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""São Carlos""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Brazil""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""SP""
  ]
}"
Yarlagadda D.V.K.; Massagué J.; Leslie C.,Discrete Representation Learning for Modeling Imaging-based Spatial Transcriptomics Data,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948400&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00416&partnerID=40&md5=84fdd67b4833f3692581633568ea8ad7,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Memorial Sloan Kettering  New York City  United States; Cornell University  New York City  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Memorial Sloan Kettering""  ""Cornell University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""New York City""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Xie B.; Park C.H.,Multi-Modal Correlated Network with Emotional Reasoning Knowledge for Social Intelligence Question-Answering,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182944684&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00331&partnerID=40&md5=8e48fc2257bcea605373f957b3061f29,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,The George Washington University  School of Engineering and Applied Science  Department of Biomedical Engineering  Washington  DC  United States; The George Washington University  School of Engineering and Applied Science  Department of Computer Science  Washington  DC  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""The George Washington University"" 
    ""School of Engineering and Applied Science"" 
    ""Department of Biomedical Engineering"" 
    ""Department of Computer Science""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Washington  DC""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Ganugula P.; Kumar Y.S.S.S.S.; Reddy N.K.S.; Chellingi P.; Thakur A.; Kasera N.; Anand C.S.,MOSAIC: Multi-Object Segmented Arbitrary Stylization Using CLIP,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182944322&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00096&partnerID=40&md5=5e37c4f43753276bc5ddb537103b750e,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Oppo Mobiles R & D Center  Hyderabad  India; Iit Hyderabad  Department of Computer Science and Engineering  India,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Oppo Mobiles R & D Center"" 
        ""Iit Hyderabad"" 
        ""Department of Computer Science and Engineering""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Hyderabad""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""India""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Sardari F.; Mustafa A.; Jackson P.J.B.; Hilton A.,PAT: Position-Aware Transformer for Dense Multi-Label Action Detection,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182951080&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00321&partnerID=40&md5=55049d7757efb47fb75ecde0a8f71476,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Surrey  Centre for Vision  Speech and Signal Processing (CVSSP)  United Kingdom,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Surrey""  ""Centre for Vision  Speech and Signal Processing (CVSSP)""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Kingdom""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Masala M.; Cudlenco N.; Rebedea T.; Leordeanu M.,Explaining Vision and Language through Graphs of Events in Space and Time,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182947260&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00302&partnerID=40&md5=b8ebad2db18ec0af4a8d1f16b0f7c925,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Institute of Mathematics of the Romanian Academy  Romania; University Politehnica of Bucharest  Romania,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Institute of Mathematics of the Romanian Academy"" 
        ""University Politehnica of Bucharest""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Bucharest""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Romania""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Sun F.; Karaoglu S.; Gevers T.,Temporally Consistent Semantic Segmentation using Spatially Aware Multi-view Semantic Fusion for Indoor RGB-D videos,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946608&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00459&partnerID=40&md5=6f17c49f4796e8853376a6ddda481477,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Amsterdam  Amsterdam  Netherlands; 3DUniversum  Amsterdam  Netherlands,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Amsterdam""  ""3DUniversum""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Amsterdam""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Netherlands""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Balaji P.; Das A.; Das S.; Dantcheva A.,Attending Generalizability in Course of Deep Fake Detection by Exploring Multi-task Learning,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945915&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00054&partnerID=40&md5=2403cfdbe6a5a249c6e21995a855cddd,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Bits Pilani  Hyderabad  India; University of North Carolina  Charlotte  NC  United States; Inria  Biot  France,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Bits Pilani"" 
    ""University of North Carolina"" 
    ""Inria""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Hyderabad"" 
    ""Charlotte"" 
    ""Biot""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""India"" 
    ""United States"" 
    ""France""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
García J.L.L.; Monroy R.; Hernández V.A.S.,An Experimental Protocol for Neural Architecture Search in Super-Resolution,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952179&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00447&partnerID=40&md5=1aab562f80e2b5d18d9c5c23c613fb36,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,School of Engineering and Sciences  Tecnologico de Monterrey  Av. Lago de Guadalupe Km 3.5  Edo. Mexico  Atizapán de Zaragoza  52926  Mexico,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""School of Engineering and Sciences""  ""Tecnologico de Monterrey""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Atizapán de Zaragoza""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Mexico""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""Av. Lago de Guadalupe Km 3.5""  ""Edo. Mexico""  ""52926""]
}"
Tran R.; Kanaujia A.; Parameswaran V.,Fast Object Detection in High-Resolution Videos,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182951486&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00159&partnerID=40&md5=df132e80807d6582c4f56504d4c53cf6,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Percipient.ai  Santa Clara  CA  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Percipient.ai""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Santa Clara"" 
    ""CA""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Park M.; Kim H.-I.; Song H.J.; Kang D.-O.,Augmenting Features via Contrastive Learning-based Generative Model for Long-Tailed Classification,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182950398&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00108&partnerID=40&md5=63d201f9851244c20ff809fb873416ca,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Electronics and Telecommunications Research Institute (ETRI)  South Korea,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Electronics and Telecommunications Research Institute""  ""ETRI""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""South Korea""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Voskou A.; Panousis K.P.; Partaourides H.; Tolias K.; Chatzis S.,A New Dataset for End-to-End Sign Language Translation: The Greek Elementary School Dataset,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946733&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00211&partnerID=40&md5=5a41facb03850a9e0355b6a03f4bae06,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Cyprus University of Technology  Cyprus; Ai Cyprus Ethical Novelties Ltd  Cyprus,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Cyprus University of Technology""  ""Ai Cyprus Ethical Novelties Ltd""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Cyprus""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Jodelet Q.; Liu X.; Phua Y.J.; Murata T.,Class-Incremental Learning using Diffusion Model for Distillation and Replay,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182949847&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00367&partnerID=40&md5=b9fe8d0a2e188662d19d9e5308d5623a,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Tokyo Institute of Technology  Department of Computer Science  Japan; Aist  Artificial Intelligence Research Center  Japan,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Tokyo Institute of Technology"" 
    ""Department of Computer Science"" 
    ""Aist"" 
    ""Artificial Intelligence Research Center""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Tokyo""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Japan""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Kim D.,CheXFusion: Effective Fusion of Multi-View Features using Transformers for Long-Tailed Chest X-Ray Classification,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946336&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00285&partnerID=40&md5=17ea3b5be6e5fb5b5922d3c48e026947,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Carnegie Mellon University  Pittsburgh  15213  PA  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Carnegie Mellon University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Pittsburgh""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""15213"" 
    ""PA""
  ]
}"
Tang L.; Li K.; He C.; Zhang Y.; Li X.,Consistency Regularization for Generalizable Source-free Domain Adaptation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182950822&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00467&partnerID=40&md5=90d86d31ddada76a000cf3f91c63ad3e,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Tsinghua Shenzhen International Graduate School  Tsinghua University  China; Nec Laboratories America  United States; Eth Zurich  Switzerland,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Tsinghua Shenzhen International Graduate School""  ""Tsinghua University""  ""Nec Laboratories America""  ""Eth Zurich""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""China""  ""United States""  ""Switzerland""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Souza B.; Aasan M.; Pedrini H.; Rivera A.R.,SelfGraphVQA: A Self-Supervised Graph Neural Network for Scene-based Question Answering,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946737&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00499&partnerID=40&md5=086ae75f13d3c4001cffca9ec3f3876d,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Campinas  Brazil; University of Oslo  Norway,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""University of Campinas"" 
        ""University of Oslo""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Brazil"" 
        ""Norway""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Dawoud Y.; Carneiro G.; Belagiannis V.,SelectNAdapt: Support Set Selection for Few-Shot Domain Adaptation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945408&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00104&partnerID=40&md5=22e142fdb78d0b4e927b257880661c7a,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Friedrich-Alexander-Universität Erlangen-Nürnberg  Erlangen  Germany; University of Surrey  United Kingdom,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Friedrich-Alexander-Universität Erlangen-Nürnberg"" 
    ""University of Surrey""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Erlangen""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Germany"" 
    ""United Kingdom""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Teeti I.; Bhargav R.S.; Singh V.; Bradley A.; Banerjee B.; Cuzzolin F.,Temporal DINO: A Self-supervised Video Strategy to Enhance Action Prediction,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182949169&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00352&partnerID=40&md5=a354bf0b6a3e918e09dde6d7df1b5241,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Oxford Brookes University  Vail  United Kingdom; Indian Institute of Technology  Bombay  India,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Oxford Brookes University"" 
    ""Indian Institute of Technology  Bombay""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Vail""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Kingdom"" 
    ""India""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Pourreza R.; Bhattacharyya A.; Panchal S.; Lee M.; Madan P.; Memisevic R.,Painter: Teaching Auto-regressive Language Models to Draw Sketches,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182949166&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00038&partnerID=40&md5=5246bbb9acba4500f9df2628e460d01b,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Qualcomm Ai Research  San Diego  CA  United States; Qualcomm Ai Research  Markham  ON  Canada,-1,"{
	""ORGANIZATION"": [""Qualcomm Ai Research""] 
	""LOCATION"": [""San Diego""  ""Markham""] 
	""COUNTRY"": [""United States""  ""Canada""] 
	""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""CA""  ""ON""]
}"
Ahmed F.; Nuwagira B.; Torlak F.; Coskunuzer B.,Topo-CXR: Chest X-ray TB and Pneumonia Screening with Topological Machine Learning,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946572&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00246&partnerID=40&md5=e92ceb54ef84836f04f0bb2f726566a0,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Ut Dallas  Dept. of Math. Sciences  United States; Ut Southwestern  Dept. of Radiology  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Ut Dallas""  ""Dept. of Math. Sciences""  ""Ut Southwestern""  ""Dept. of Radiology""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Bicsi L.; Alexe B.; Ionescu R.T.; Leordeanu M.,JEDI: Joint Expert Distillation in a Semi-Supervised Multi-Dataset Student-Teacher Scenario for Video Action Recognition,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945087&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00102&partnerID=40&md5=9833d7558525d75ab43cf92f0329ab41,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Bucharest  Romania; Politehnica University of Bucharest  Romania; Institute of Mathematics of the Romanian Academy  Romania,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Bucharest""  ""Politehnica University of Bucharest""  ""Institute of Mathematics of the Romanian Academy""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Romania""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Tausch F.; Wagner J.; Klaus S.,Pollinators as Data Collectors: Estimating Floral Diversity with Bees and Computer Vision,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182947786&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00071&partnerID=40&md5=3c248e54bf98a39e4d021611be1d7204,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Karlsruhe Institute of Technology  Karlsruhe  Germany; Apic.ai  Karlsruhe  Germany,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Karlsruhe Institute of Technology"" 
        ""Apic.ai""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Karlsruhe""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Germany""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Besbes M.D.E.; Vahidi Ferdousi Z.; Tabia H.; Fradi M.,2D Cross-View Object Segmentation and Perceptual Grouping in Computer-Aided Design Drawings,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182944154&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00190&partnerID=40&md5=8e2f4a4e1485d1efe6d23fee211eef17,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Capgemini  France; Univ Paris Saclay  France,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Capgemini""  ""Univ Paris Saclay""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""France""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Simone G.D.; Foggia P.; Saggese A.; Vento M.,Autonomous mobile robot for automatic out of stock detection in a supermarket,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182947941&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00197&partnerID=40&md5=c81f3cd9a643c431a05d3c40936f580f,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Salerno  Italy,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""University of Salerno""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Italy""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Mukhoti J.; Lin T.-Y.; Chen B.-C.; Shah A.; Torr P.H.S.; Dokania P.K.; Lim S.-N.,Raising the Bar on the Evaluation of Out-of-Distribution Detection,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946453&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00471&partnerID=40&md5=468a779252638d17b848e6fc6dbfd236,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Oxford  United Kingdom; Meta Ai  United States,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Oxford""  ""Meta Ai""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""United Kingdom""  ""United States""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Kumar A.; Anand K.; Mandloi S.; Mishra A.; Thakur A.; Kasera N.; Prathosh A.P.,CoroNetGAN: Controlled Pruning of GANs via Hypernetworks,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945400&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00136&partnerID=40&md5=7363a99d04811e67f25ab613742d63eb,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Oppo Mobiles R & D Center  Hyderabad  India; Indian Institute of Science  Bangalore  India,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Oppo Mobiles R & D Center"" 
    ""Indian Institute of Science""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Hyderabad"" 
    ""Bangalore""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""India""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Vats V.; Jerripothula K.R.,Adversarial Examples with Specular Highlights,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182953295&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00388&partnerID=40&md5=e880f2695c85565c0311988e4a3ec79f,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of California  Santa Cruz  United States; Indraprastha Institute of Information Technology  Delhi  India,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of California"" 
    ""Indraprastha Institute of Information Technology""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Santa Cruz"" 
    ""Delhi""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United States"" 
    ""India""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Sufian A.; Ghosh A.; Barman D.; Leo M.; Distante C.; Li B.,FewFaceNet: A Lightweight Few-Shot Learning-based Incremental Face Authentication for Edge Cameras,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952363&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00216&partnerID=40&md5=df64700a61d9932cc5aeb779134dd10c,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Gour Banga  English Bazar  India; Visva-Bharati  Santiniketan  India; CNR-ISASI  Lecce  73100  Italy; Loughborough University  Loughborough  United Kingdom,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Gour Banga""  ""Visva-Bharati""  ""CNR-ISASI""  ""Loughborough University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""English Bazar""  ""Santiniketan""  ""Lecce""  ""Loughborough""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""India""  ""Italy""  ""United Kingdom""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""73100""]
}"
Farag M.; Kierdorf J.; Roscher R.,Inductive Conformal Prediction for Harvest-Readiness Classification of Cauliflower Plants: A Comparative Study of Uncertainty Quantification Methods,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182949594&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00072&partnerID=40&md5=8e0ea897ec728564b31d6580d9401c94,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Forschungszentrum Jülich GmbH  Data Science for Crop Systems  Institute of Bio- and Geosciences  IBG-2: Plant Sciences  Germany; University of Bonn  Remote Sensing Group  Institute of Geodesy and Geoinformation  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Forschungszentrum Jülich GmbH""  ""University of Bonn""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Germany""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""Data Science for Crop Systems""  ""Institute of Bio- and Geosciences""  ""IBG-2: Plant Sciences""  ""Remote Sensing Group""  ""Institute of Geodesy and Geoinformation""]
}"
Hall M.; Gustafson L.; Adcock A.; Misra I.; Ross C.,Vision-Language Models Performing Zero-Shot Tasks Exhibit Disparities Between Gender Groups,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945271&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00294&partnerID=40&md5=8f3257cdd511d939a6b4d72145ccc03e,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Meta Ai  United States,-1,"{
   ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Meta Ai""] 
   ""LOCATION"": [] 
   ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""] 
   ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Martins T.B.; Civera J.,Ray-Patch: An Efficient Querying for Light Field Transformers,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182947172&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00124&partnerID=40&md5=7179c600f21a157edd4342416f75b82e,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Zaragoza  I3A  Spain,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Zaragoza""  ""I3A""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Spain""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Chandra Sekhar V.; Gautam A.; Viswanath P.; Sreeja S.R.; Rama Krishna Sai G.,TSOSVNet: Teacher-student collaborative knowledge distillation for Online Signature Verification,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945828&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00082&partnerID=40&md5=3064098a2d96e0538f2145b4f10b166e,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,IIIT-SriCity  Andhra Pradesh  India; BITS-Pilani  Pilani  333031  India; IIT-Tirupati  Andhra Pradesh  India,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""IIIT-SriCity"" 
    ""BITS-Pilani"" 
    ""IIT-Tirupati""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Pilani""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""India""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""Andhra Pradesh"" 
    ""333031""
  ]
}"
Tal O.B.; Haviv A.; Bermano A.H.,OMG-Attack: Self-Supervised On-Manifold Generation of Transferable Evasion Attacks,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945709&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00397&partnerID=40&md5=db0b7b16f1ff1065dd4a8c03d8bf2079,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Tel Aviv University  Israel,-1,"```json
{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Tel Aviv University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Tel Aviv""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Israel""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}
```"
Salmon B.; Krull A.,Direct Unsupervised Denoising,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182953577&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00415&partnerID=40&md5=a57278f1b27f4b1de561b599bfe57eef,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Birmingham  Birmingham  B15 2TT  United Kingdom,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Birmingham""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Birmingham""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Kingdom""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""B15 2TT""]
}"
Seo H.; Lee M.; Cheong W.; Yoon H.; Kim S.; Kang M.,Enhancing Multi-Label Long-Tailed Classification on Chest X-Rays through ML-GCN Augmentation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182951552&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00290&partnerID=40&md5=b105d4a6a5b2e665a524478bc8ce6c4d,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Seoul National University  South Korea; Ipai  Seoul National University  South Korea; Seoul National University  Department of Mathematical Sciences  South Korea,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Seoul National University"" 
        ""Seoul National University"" 
        ""Seoul National University"" 
        ""Department of Mathematical Sciences""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Ipai""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""South Korea"" 
        ""South Korea"" 
        ""South Korea""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Liu Z.; Wang Y.; Chu X.; Dong N.; Qi S.; Ling H.,A Simple and Generic Framework for Feature Distillation via Channel-wise Transformation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948829&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00121&partnerID=40&md5=9842a4fec4ac279b9d65c8c8080ba634,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Peking University  Wangxuan Institute of Computer Technology  China; Chong Qing Changan Automobile Co.  Ltd  China; Stony Brook University  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Peking University"" 
    ""Wangxuan Institute of Computer Technology"" 
    ""Chong Qing Changan Automobile Co.  Ltd"" 
    ""Stony Brook University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""China"" 
    ""China"" 
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Karvounas G.; Kyriazis N.; Oikonomidis I.; Argyros A.,Dynamic Multiview Refinement of 3D Hand Datasets using Differentiable Ray Tracing,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946926&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00340&partnerID=40&md5=19366ecf6472df948c8e1435c9c472c6,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Institute of Computer Science  Forth  Greece; University of Crete  Computer Science Department  Heraklion  Greece,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Institute of Computer Science""  ""University of Crete""  ""Computer Science Department""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Forth""  ""Heraklion""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Greece""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Grimaldi M.; Ganji D.C.; Lazarevich I.; Sah S.,Accelerating Deep Neural Networks via Semi-Structured Activation Sparsity,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952517&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00127&partnerID=40&md5=3ecdccd53d6c536de1a833bd9139ebdc,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Deeplite  Canada,-1,"{
   ""ORGANIZATION"": ""Deeplite"" 
   ""COUNTRY"": ""Canada""
}"
Choi W.; Im S.,Dynamic neural network for multi-task learning searching across diverse network topologies,Proceedings of the IEEE Computer Society Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85185401007&doi=10.1109%2fCVPR52729.2023.00368&partnerID=40&md5=42c63200a520f71ea637dc553fe257d2,nanIEEE Computer Society,Department of Electrical Engineering & Computer Science  DGIST  Daegu  South Korea,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Department of Electrical Engineering & Computer Science"" 
    ""DGIST""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Daegu""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""South Korea""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Singh A.,Transformer-Based Sensor Fusion for Autonomous Driving: A Survey,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182947283&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00355&partnerID=40&md5=62b6380bf2279e297174e2f4beab1eb0,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Motional  Carnegie Mellon University  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Motional""  ""Carnegie Mellon University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Liu R.; Zhang J.; Peng K.; Zheng J.; Cao K.; Chen Y.; Yang K.; Stiefelhagen R.,Open Scene Understanding: Grounded Situation Recognition Meets Segment Anything for Helping People with Visual Impairments,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946192&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00200&partnerID=40&md5=7c988e5548cb8cd6fd51ce3c552f09bf,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Karlsruhe Institute of Technology  Germany; Hunan University  China,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Karlsruhe Institute of Technology"" 
        ""Hunan University""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Germany"" 
        ""China""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Trinci T.; Bianconcini T.; Sarti L.; Taccari L.; Sambo F.,Cross-model temporal cooperation via saliency maps for efficient frame classification,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182951667&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00125&partnerID=40&md5=9692309de60dc1d99bd3193fb6252720,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Verizon Connect; University of Florence  Italy,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Verizon Connect"" 
        ""University of Florence""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Italy""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Cordes K.; Broszio H.,Camera-Based Road Snow Coverage Estimation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948929&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00433&partnerID=40&md5=39b84436a1a59fd0aeb023d8f9d735e3,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Viscoda GmbH,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Viscoda GmbH""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Wang X.; Chu X.; Han C.; Zhang X.,SCSC: Spatial Cross-scale Convolution Module to Strengthen both CNNs and Transformers,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182950970&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00081&partnerID=40&md5=f087ba9544d86cbb1f5a7bfeb3dc9902,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,The University of Maryland  College Park  MD  United States; Megvii Technology  Beijing  China,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Maryland""  ""Megvii Technology""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""College Park""  ""Beijing""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""  ""China""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""MD""]
}"
Qammaz A.; Argyros A.A.,A Unified Approach for Occlusion Tolerant 3D Facial Pose Capture and Gaze Estimation using MocapNETs,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952626&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00342&partnerID=40&md5=3bcdd21e564053aeb169891832b1be2b,1.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Crete  Computer Science Department  Crete  Heraklion  Greece; Forth  Institute of Computer Science  Crete  Heraklion  Greece,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Crete""  ""Computer Science Department""  ""Forth""  ""Institute of Computer Science""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Crete""  ""Heraklion""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Greece""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Myers A.; Taylor C.; Jacobs E.; Miolane N.,Geodesic Regression Characterizes 3D Shape Changes in the Female Brain During Menstruation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948937&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00268&partnerID=40&md5=024dd2b2e1bc97bf4924b6a2ed815305,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Uc Santa Barbara  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Uc Santa Barbara""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Pagé-Fortin M.,Class-Incremental Learning of Plant and Disease Detection: Growing Branches with Knowledge Distillation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948498&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00066&partnerID=40&md5=3956feb70a3b4b0fad56a0d9faec245c,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Laval University  Canada,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Laval University""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""Canada""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Gavrikov P.; Keuper J.,On the Interplay of Convolutional Padding and Adversarial Robustness,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182947200&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00430&partnerID=40&md5=3787903dc4f613f4f494a9544dcf1387,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Offenburg University  Imla  Germany; Fraunhofer Itwm  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Offenburg University""  ""Fraunhofer Itwm""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Imla""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Germany""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Zheng J.; Yang L.; Li Y.; Yang K.; Wang Z.; Zhou J.,Lightweight Vision Transformer with Spatial and Channel Enhanced Self-Attention,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948132&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00162&partnerID=40&md5=dec3d12a8b13f9cd51077e34cc35e608,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Electronic Science and Technology of China  Chengdu  China; Academy of Military Sciences  Defense Innovation Institute  Beijing  China,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of Electronic Science and Technology of China"" 
    ""Academy of Military Sciences"" 
    ""Defense Innovation Institute""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Chengdu"" 
    ""Beijing""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""China""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Xiang J.; Shlizerman E.,TKIL: Tangent Kernel Optimization for Class Balanced Incremental Learning,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182944331&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00379&partnerID=40&md5=d637300b7d0aab675c4f037de4d80700,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Washington  Department of Electrical & Computer Engineering  Seattle  United States; University of Washington  Department of Electrical & Computer Engineering  Department of Applied Mathematics  Seattle  United States,-1,
Nguyen-Mau T.-H.; Huynh T.-L.; Le T.-D.; Nguyen H.-D.; Tran M.-T.,Advanced Augmentation and Ensemble Approaches for Classifying Long-Tailed Multi-Label Chest X-Rays,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948412&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00288&partnerID=40&md5=fca8e212ebbc0da19629f910702ab649,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Science  VNU-HCM  Ho Chi Minh City  Viet Nam; Viet Nam National University  Ho Chi Minh City  Viet Nam,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of Science  VNU-HCM"" 
    ""Viet Nam National University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Ho Chi Minh City""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Viet Nam""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
González C.; Ayobi N.; Escallón F.; Baldovino-Chiquillo L.; Wilches-Mogollón M.; Pasos D.; Ramírez N.; Pinzón J.; Sarmiento O.; Quistberg D.A.; Arbeláez P.,STRIDE: Street View-based Environmental Feature Detection and Pedestrian Collision Prediction,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182951693&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00347&partnerID=40&md5=7a17f371a4e15df8ee947947606b9186,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Universidad de Los Andes  Center for Research and Formation in Artificial Intelligence  Colombia; Universidad de Los Andes  School of Engineering  Colombia; Universidad de Los Andes  School of Medicine  Colombia; Universidad de Los Andes  School of Economics  Colombia; Pontificia Universidad Javeriana  School of Architecture and Design  Colombia; Drexel University  Dornsife School of Public Health  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Universidad de Los Andes"" 
    ""Center for Research and Formation in Artificial Intelligence"" 
    ""Pontificia Universidad Javeriana"" 
    ""Drexel University"" 
    ""Dornsife School of Public Health""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Colombia"" 
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""School of Engineering"" 
    ""School of Medicine"" 
    ""School of Economics"" 
    ""School of Architecture and Design""
  ]
}"
Manousaki V.; Bacharidis K.; Papoutsakis K.; Argyros A.,VLMAH: Visual-Linguistic Modeling of Action History for Effective Action Anticipation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182952934&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00206&partnerID=40&md5=1a270f8702e717092830ef853cc941d4,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Crete  Computer Science Department  Greece; Institute of Computer Science  Forth  Greece; Hellenic Mediterranean University  Department of Management  Science & Technology  Greece,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of Crete"" 
    ""Computer Science Department"" 
    ""Institute of Computer Science"" 
    ""Hellenic Mediterranean University"" 
    ""Department of Management  Science & Technology""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Greece"" 
    ""Forth""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Mikhailov I.; Chauveau B.; Bourdel N.; Bartoli A.,Sharing is Caring: Concurrent Interactive Segmentation and Model Training using a Joint Model,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945737&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00257&partnerID=40&md5=81e7cdad9b50f5c2b1c09394386e2adf,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Université Clermont Auvergne  France; Surgar  Clermont-Ferrand  France; Chu de Clermont-Ferrand  France,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Université Clermont Auvergne"" 
    ""Chu de Clermont-Ferrand""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Clermont-Ferrand""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""France""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""Surgar""
  ]
}"
Sakaino H.,Semantically Enhanced Scene Captions with Physical and Weather Condition Changes,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945959&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00393&partnerID=40&md5=205f372dcce4992ab90751c5802b19a9,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Weathernews Inc.  Visual Recognition Group  Weather Transportation Lab.,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Weathernews Inc.""  ""Visual Recognition Group""  ""Weather Transportation Lab""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Shtedritski A.; Vedaldi A.; Rupprecth C.,Learning Universal Semantic Correspondences with No Supervision and Automatic Data Curation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945203&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00100&partnerID=40&md5=a9c46278061ee32004c04422ac6f110f,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Visual Geometry Group  University of Oxford  United Kingdom,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Visual Geometry Group"" 
        ""University of Oxford""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""United Kingdom""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Diba A.; Sharma V.; Arzani M.M.; Van Gool L.,Spatio-Temporal Convolution-Attention Video Network,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182946658&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00093&partnerID=40&md5=b1a6834efa6b6abcd47798ad4864e0f5,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Ku Leuven  Belgium; Sony Ai; Massachusetts Institute of Technology  United States; Eth Zurich  Switzerland,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Ku Leuven""  ""Sony Ai""  ""Massachusetts Institute of Technology""  ""Eth Zurich""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""Belgium""  ""United States""  ""Switzerland""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Rajapaksa S.; Uwabeza Vianney J.M.; Castro R.; Khalvati F.; Aich S.,Using Large Text To Image Models with Structured Prompts for Skin Disease Identification: A Case Study,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182944237&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00284&partnerID=40&md5=9563b85b357d46ce3c434b8df5878108,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Yuko Ai Inc.  Toronto  ON  Canada; University of Toronto  ON  Canada; SickKids Hospital  Toronto  ON  Canada; Vector Institute  Toronto  ON  Canada; Carnegie Mellon University  Robotics Institute  Pittsburgh  PA  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Yuko Ai Inc."" 
    ""University of Toronto"" 
    ""SickKids Hospital"" 
    ""Vector Institute"" 
    ""Carnegie Mellon University"" 
    ""Robotics Institute""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Toronto"" 
    ""Toronto"" 
    ""Toronto"" 
    ""Toronto"" 
    ""Pittsburgh""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Canada"" 
    ""Canada"" 
    ""Canada"" 
    ""Canada"" 
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""ON"" 
    ""ON"" 
    ""ON"" 
    ""ON"" 
    ""PA""
  ]
}"
Jahagirdar S.; Mathew M.; Karatzas D.; Jawahar C.V.,Understanding Video Scenes through Text: Insights from Text-based Video Question Answering,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182948794&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00500&partnerID=40&md5=e56b75381e851706d3c00f1883f694ff,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Iiit Hyderabad  Cvit  India; Wadhwani Ai; Uab  Computer Vision Center  Spain,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Iiit Hyderabad""  ""Cvit""  ""Wadhwani Ai""  ""Uab""  ""Computer Vision Center""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""India""  ""Spain""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Sincan O.M.; Camgoz N.C.; Bowden R.,Is context all you need? Scaling Neural Sign Language Translation to Large Domains of Discourse,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945162&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00210&partnerID=40&md5=13dc741d6e4c4107b474b7b513f26d76,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Surrey  United Kingdom; Meta Reality Labs  Switzerland,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Surrey""  ""Meta Reality Labs""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""United Kingdom""  ""Switzerland""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Holm F.; Ghazaei G.; Czempiel T.; Özsoy E.; Saur S.; Navab N.,Dynamic Scene Graph Representation for Surgical Video,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182945563&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00015&partnerID=40&md5=7d8c0928761fd617f7e5e4fa28cec269,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Technical University Munich  Computer Aided Medical Procedures  Germany; Carl Zeiss Ag  Oberkochen  Germany; Carl Zeiss Meditec Ag  Jena  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Technical University Munich""  ""Computer Aided Medical Procedures""  ""Carl Zeiss Ag""  ""Carl Zeiss Meditec Ag""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Oberkochen""  ""Jena""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Germany""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Dulau I.; Helmer C.; Delcourt C.; Beurton-Aimar M.,Ensuring a connected structure for Retinal Vessels Deep-Learning Segmentation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182947465&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00250&partnerID=40&md5=0ed16744d96c2b3b63d3d81b3792502f,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Bordeaux University  LaBRI Umr 5800  France; Bordeaux University  Inserm U1219  France,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Bordeaux University""  ""LaBRI Umr 5800""  ""Inserm U1219""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Bordeaux""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""France""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Yatbaz H.Y.; Dianati M.; Koufos K.; Woodman R.,Introspection of 2D Object Detection using Processed Neural Activation Patterns in Automated Driving Systems,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182947224&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00437&partnerID=40&md5=433797d076f1af620aab834f3aa21567,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Warwick  Wmg  United Kingdom; Queen's University of Belfast  School of Electronics  Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EEECS)  United Kingdom,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Warwick""  ""Wmg""  ""Queen's University of Belfast""  ""School of Electronics  Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EEECS)""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Kingdom""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Santos F.A.O.; Zanchettin C.,Exploring Image Classification Robustness and Interpretability with Right for the Right Reasons Data Augmentation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182937607&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00448&partnerID=40&md5=ff43519e4314a9b8c5dd4e27f4d08b43,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Universidade Federal de Pernambuco  Cidade Universitária  Centro de Informática  PE  Recife  50740-560  Brazil,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Universidade Federal de Pernambuco"" 
        ""Centro de Informática""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Cidade Universitária"" 
        ""Recife""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Brazil""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
        ""PE"" 
        ""50740-560""
    ]
}"
Schiatti L.; Gori M.; Schrimpf M.; Cappagli G.; Morelli F.; Signorini S.; Katz B.; Barbu A.,Modeling Visual Impairments with Artificial Neural Networks: a Review,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182934610&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00213&partnerID=40&md5=1f32e1b958bf195de3efe4d9c9bc064d,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Csail  Cbmm  Massachusetts Institute of Technology  United States; Uvip  Istituto Italiano di Tecnologia  Italy; NeuroX Institute  Epfl  Lausanne  Switzerland; Irccs Mondino Foundation  Italy; Dbbs  University of Pavia  Italy,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Csail""  ""Cbmm""  ""Massachusetts Institute of Technology""  ""Uvip""  ""Istituto Italiano di Tecnologia""  ""NeuroX Institute""  ""Epfl""  ""Irccs Mondino Foundation""  ""Dbbs""  ""University of Pavia""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Lausanne""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""  ""Italy""  ""Switzerland""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Hilt P.; Zarvandi M.; Kaziakhmedov E.; Bhide S.; Laptin M.; Pape C.; Kreshuk A.,Reinforcement learning for instance segmentation with high-level priors,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182938934&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00423&partnerID=40&md5=f040092865fa2d51c7f5347c7c7d018d,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Heidelberg University  Germany; Embl Heidelberg  Germany; University Göttingen  Germany,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Heidelberg University""  ""Embl Heidelberg""  ""University Göttingen""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [""Germany""] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Xing X.; Groh K.; Karaoglu S.; Gevers T.,Intrinsic Appearance Decomposition Using Point Cloud Representation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182938538&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00457&partnerID=40&md5=11549d5c2682ad29fc49e950375def8d,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Amsterdam  UvA-Bosch Delta Lab  Netherlands; Robert Bosch GmbH  Bosch Center of Artificial Intelligence  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Amsterdam""  ""UvA-Bosch Delta Lab""  ""Robert Bosch GmbH""  ""Bosch Center of Artificial Intelligence""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Netherlands""  ""Germany""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Hu Y.; Ye X.; Liu Y.; Kundu S.; Datta G.; Mutnuri S.; Asavisanu N.; Ayanian N.; Psounis K.; Beerel P.,FireFly: A Synthetic Dataset for Ember Detection in Wildfire,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182935265&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00406&partnerID=40&md5=cd915b82de306a25e3078980a05c6636,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Southern California  United States; University of California  Irvine  United States; Intel Labs  San Diego  United States; Brown University  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Southern California""  ""University of California  Irvine""  ""Intel Labs""  ""Brown University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""San Diego""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Gueze A.; Ospici M.; Rohmer D.; Cani M.-P.,Floor Plan Reconstruction from Sparse Views: Combining Graph Neural Network with Constrained Diffusion,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182938535&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00173&partnerID=40&md5=2886ca4dad29c4f7fb21ff28679dd2b1,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Institut Polytechnique de Paris  Lix  École Polytechnique  France; Homiwoo  France,-1,"```json
{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Institut Polytechnique de Paris"" 
    ""Lix"" 
    ""École Polytechnique""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Homiwoo""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""France""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}
```"
Arcega Rustia D.J.; Jansen G.A.; Hageraats S.; Peller J.; Van De Zedde R.; Marchennay C.; Sangster W.; Blokker G.,Rapid tomato DUS trait analysis using an optimized mobile-based coarse-to-fine instance segmentation algorithm,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182937320&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00070&partnerID=40&md5=6017fde4f1145ddfc5a65b24eee4f8e8,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Wageningen University and Research  Wageningen Plant Research  Wageningen  Netherlands; Naktuinbouw  Roelofarendsveen  Netherlands,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Wageningen University and Research""  ""Wageningen Plant Research""  ""Naktuinbouw""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Wageningen""  ""Roelofarendsveen""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Netherlands""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Matsuda S.; Techasarntikul N.; Shimonishi H.,Multi-Camera 3D Position Estimation using Conditional Random Field,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182943850&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00205&partnerID=40&md5=676400cc1daae1dabfa94593d16f6da1,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Osaka University  Graduate School of Information Science and Technology  Japan; Osaka University  Cybermedia Center  Japan,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Osaka University"" 
    ""Graduate School of Information Science and Technology"" 
    ""Osaka University"" 
    ""Cybermedia Center""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Japan"" 
    ""Japan""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Bhardwaj K.; Cheng H.-P.; Priyadarshi S.; Li Z.,ZiCo-BC: A Bias Corrected Zero-Shot NAS for Vision Tasks,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182943334&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00145&partnerID=40&md5=a4d9676dd009223eca80e35b79fca833,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Qualcomm Ai Research  San Diego  92121  CA  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Qualcomm Ai Research""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""San Diego""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""92121"" 
    ""CA""
  ]
}"
Onghena P.; Gigli L.; Velasco-Forero S.,Rotation-invariant Hierarchical Segmentation on Poincaré Ball for 3D Point Cloud,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182942121&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00192&partnerID=40&md5=00eac91a17828cc2f6e4ed479838c2b3,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,TheCrossProduct; Psl Research University  Mines Paris  France,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""TheCrossProduct""  ""Psl Research University""  ""Mines Paris""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""France""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Ambati R.; Akhtar N.; Mian A.; Rawat Y.S.,PRAT: PRofiling Adversarial aTtacks,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182937560&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00394&partnerID=40&md5=6b2ccdb04d87a4c1f3f53caf98b97e13,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Central Florida  United States; The University of Western Australia  Australia,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of Central Florida"" 
    ""The University of Western Australia""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United States"" 
    ""Australia""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Wagner B.; Pellerin D.; Huet S.,Comparative Study of Natural Replay and Experience Replay in Online Object Detection,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182944022&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00386&partnerID=40&md5=8ea1f362c081ba3c19577d0594c85f11,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Univ. Grenoble Alpes  CNRS  Grenoble Inp  GIPSA-lab  Grenoble  38000  France,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Univ. Grenoble Alpes""  ""CNRS""  ""Grenoble Inp""  ""GIPSA-lab""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [""Grenoble""] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""France""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""38000""]
}"
Gao T.; Long R.,Accumulation Knowledge Distillation for Conditional GAN Compression,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182934621&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00140&partnerID=40&md5=333924b57adab9374bc8a6a6c2c97c19,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Alibaba Group  China,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Alibaba Group""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""China""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Oorloff T.; Yacoob Y.,Expressive Talking Head Video Encoding in StyleGAN2 Latent Space,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182938824&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00322&partnerID=40&md5=5cb2398b20f67b01bb46dfce3f79f73e,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Maryland  United States,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Maryland""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Vojir T.; Sochman J.; Aljundi R.; Matas J.,Calibrated Out-of-Distribution Detection with a Generic Representation,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182938700&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00485&partnerID=40&md5=56c3aad21aa676de48024bff69287db6,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Cmp Visual Recognition Group  Fee  Czech Technical University  Prague  Czech Republic; Toyota Motor Europe  Brussels  Belgium,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Cmp Visual Recognition Group"" 
    ""Toyota Motor Europe""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Czech Technical University"" 
    ""Prague"" 
    ""Brussels""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Czech Republic"" 
    ""Belgium""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Warchocki J.; Oprescu T.; Wang Y.; Dǎmǎcuş A.; Misterka P.; Bruintjes R.-J.; Lengyel A.; Strafforello O.; Van Gemert J.,Benchmarking Data Efficiency and Computational Efficiency of Temporal Action Localization Models,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182938425&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00323&partnerID=40&md5=f369cf44f0afff4c1a18f1cc6061a598,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Computer Vision Lab  Delft University of Technology  Delft  Netherlands,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Computer Vision Lab""  ""Delft University of Technology""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Delft""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Netherlands""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Desai C.; Akalwadi N.; Joshi A.; Malagi S.; Mandi C.; Tabib R.A.; Patil U.; Mudenagudi U.,LightNet: Generative Model for Enhancement of Low-Light Images,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182935153&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00237&partnerID=40&md5=68164f5cba9ac6652d313a54bfbec8eb,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Kle Technological University  Center of Excellence in Visual Intelligence (CEVI)  Karnataka  Hubballi  India,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Kle Technological University"" 
    ""Center of Excellence in Visual Intelligence (CEVI)""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Karnataka"" 
    ""Hubballi""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""India""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Bastico M.; Ryckelynck D.; Corté L.; Tillier Y.; Decencière E.,A Simple and Robust Framework for Cross-Modality Medical Image Segmentation applied to Vision Transformers,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182935676&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00446&partnerID=40&md5=04e33a217f8640f04c59612d3abba2a3,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Centre des Matériaux (MAT)  UMR7633  CNRS  Evry  91003  France; Mines Paris  Université Psl  France; Centre de Mise en Forme des Matériaux (CEMEF)  UMR7635  CNRS  Sophia Antipolis  06904  France; Centre de Morphologie Mathématique (CMM)  Fontainebleau  77300  France,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Centre des Matériaux (MAT)""  ""UMR7633""  ""CNRS""  ""Mines Paris""  ""Université PSL""  ""Centre de Mise en Forme des Matériaux (CEMEF)""  ""UMR7635""  ""Centre de Morphologie Mathématique (CMM)""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [""Evry""  ""Sophia Antipolis""  ""Fontainebleau""] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""France""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""91003""  ""06904""  ""77300""]
}"
Aguilar E.; Raducanu B.; Radeva P.; Van De Weijer J.,Continual Evidential Deep Learning for Out-of-Distribution Detection,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182939631&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00369&partnerID=40&md5=53a2188d4543226b700b7a7d6d1a98ff,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Universidad Católica Del Norte  Dept. de Ingeniería de Sistemas y Computación  Antofagasta  Chile; Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona  Computer Vision Center  Barcelona  Spain; Universitat de Barcelona  Dept. de Matemàtiques i Informàtica  Barcelona  Spain,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Universidad Católica Del Norte"" 
    ""Computer Vision Center"" 
    ""Universitat de Barcelona""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Dept. de Ingeniería de Sistemas y Computación"" 
    ""Antofagasta"" 
    ""Barcelona"" 
    ""Dept. de Matemàtiques i Informàtica""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Chile"" 
    ""Spain"" 
    ""Spain""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona""
  ]
}"
Kwolek B.,Continuous Hand Gesture Recognition for Human-Robot Collaborative Assembly,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182939592&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00214&partnerID=40&md5=41dc555d94299c55be9b4d4465e9fb5c,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Agh University of Krakow  30 Mickiewicza Av.  Krakow  30-059  Poland,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Agh University of Krakow""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""30 Mickiewicza Av."" 
    ""Krakow""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Poland""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""30-059""
  ]
}"
Zhang H.; Whittaker E.; Kitagishi I.,Extending TrOCR for Text Localization-Free OCR of Full-Page Scanned Receipt Images,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182944137&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00160&partnerID=40&md5=41f1201b79a961f0d8d878a5b953593e,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Nagoya University  Japan; K.K. Best Path Research; Money Forward  Inc.  Japan,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Nagoya University""  ""K.K. Best Path Research""  ""Money Forward  Inc.""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Japan""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Tiwari A.; Singhal A.; Shigwan S.J.; Kumar Singh R.,Deep Learning Framework using Sparse Diffusion MRI for Diagnosis of Frontotemporal Dementia,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182942756&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00413&partnerID=40&md5=fd0772ad188454057301de6f94bb5265,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Shiv Nadar Institution of Eminence  Department of Computer Science and Engineering  Delhi NCR  India,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Shiv Nadar Institution of Eminence"" 
    ""Department of Computer Science and Engineering""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Delhi NCR""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""India""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Ebert N.; Stricker D.; Wasenmüller O.,Transformer-based Detection of Microorganisms on High-Resolution Petri Dish Images,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182935949&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00428&partnerID=40&md5=9d9a19c4c1e86ee3199551a13b84a449,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Mannheim University for Applied Science  Germany; Rptu Kaiserslautern-Landau  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Mannheim University for Applied Science""  ""Rptu Kaiserslautern-Landau""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Germany""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Merkle N.; Bahmanyar R.; Henry C.; Azimi S.M.; Yuan X.; Schopferer S.; Gstaiger V.; Auer S.; Schneibel A.; Wieland M.; Kraft T.,Drones4Good: Supporting Disaster Relief Through Remote Sensing and AI,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182942510&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00407&partnerID=40&md5=b0cc1e2f020eb27e3dd1b6f1856412d1,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,German Aerospace Center (DLR)  Remote Sensing Technology Institute  Germany; German Aerospace Center (DLR)  Institute of Flight Systems  Germany; German Aerospace Center (DLR)  Remote Sensing Data Center  Germany; German Aerospace Center (DLR)  Institute of Optical Sensor Systems  Germany,-1,"```json
{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""German Aerospace Center (DLR)"" 
    ""Remote Sensing Technology Institute"" 
    ""Institute of Flight Systems"" 
    ""Remote Sensing Data Center"" 
    ""Institute of Optical Sensor Systems""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Germany""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}
```"
Villegas-Suarez A.M.; Lopez C.; Sipiran I.,MatchMakerNet: Enabling Fragment Matching for Cultural Heritage Analysis,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182936936&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00178&partnerID=40&md5=1721210086f154d3723a0574b2cb1d8e,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Universidad de Ingenieria y Tecnologia - Utec  Lima  Peru; University of Chile  Department of Computer Science  Santiago  Chile,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Universidad de Ingenieria y Tecnologia - Utec"" 
    ""University of Chile  Department of Computer Science""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Lima"" 
    ""Santiago""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Peru"" 
    ""Chile""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Bhattacharya S.; Bhattacharya A.; Shahnawaz S.,Generating Synthetic Computed Tomography (CT) Images to Improve the Performance of Machine Learning Model for Pediatric Abdominal Anomaly Detection,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182943627&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00418&partnerID=40&md5=0480293b0aa87a6f98dbbc3516f93704,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Jadavpur University  India,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Jadavpur University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""India""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Saha S.; Perera R.; Seneviratne S.; Malepathirana T.; Rasnayaka S.; Geethika D.; Sim T.; Halgamuge S.,Undercover Deepfakes: Detecting Fake Segments in Videos,Proceedings - 2023 IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops  ICCVW 2023,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85182936893&doi=10.1109%2fICCVW60793.2023.00048&partnerID=40&md5=401dc6963c7b3f81924d7c23b51cbc73,0.0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,National University of Singapore  Singapore; University of Melbourne  Australia,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""National University of Singapore"" 
    ""University of Melbourne""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Singapore""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Australia""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
