Alantali M.A.; Rafiq H.; Alzarouni S.A.; Qureshi O.A.; Rodriguez-Ubinas E.,Wind Speed Effect on the Performance of Free-Standing PV Modules in Hot Desert Climate,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183469619&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374470&partnerID=40&md5=77b7bd3c1ba7864c2cede92cecbcf701,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  Dew A R&d Centre  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"```json
{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority"" 
    ""Dew A R&d Centre""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Dubai""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}
```"
Ali A.A.; El-Keblawy A.; Zhang D.; Tabet N.,Use of Agrivoltaics to Enhance Cucumber Production in the Hot and Arid Climate of UAE: A Sustainable Approach for Food and Clean Energy Security,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183457195&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374503&partnerID=40&md5=79a9fe05e6c5d2cdacc12235e4619b94,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,College of Engineering  University of Sharjah  Environemtnal Science & Engineering  Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates; College of Sciences  University of Sharjah  Department of Applied Biology  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates; College of Sciences  University of Sharjah  Department of Sustainable & Renewable Energy Engineering  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates; College of Sciences  University of Sharjah  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""College of Engineering"" 
    ""University of Sharjah"" 
    ""Environemtnal Science & Engineering"" 
    ""Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering"" 
    ""College of Sciences"" 
    ""Department of Applied Biology"" 
    ""Department of Sustainable & Renewable Energy Engineering""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Sharjah""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Saleem M.; Akram M.U.,Detection of hemorrhages for diagnosis of malarial retinopathy,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923186724&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020939&partnerID=40&md5=146d0e088c87f5978f755f07e1ef0f83,3Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Department of Computer Engineering  National University of Sciences and Technology  Islamabad  Pakistan,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Department of Computer Engineering""  ""National University of Sciences and Technology""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Islamabad""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Pakistan""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Alshehhi B.; Baloch A.A.B.; Albadwawi O.; Parida B.; Sundaray M.; Alberts V.,Consolidation of Temperature Coefficients of Perovskite-Based Absorbers,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183461217&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374536&partnerID=40&md5=5903bb18d9b997275fd978a0bb933e3a,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Research and Development Center  Dubai Electricity and Water Authority (DEWA)  Dubai  United Arab Emirates; Kg Reddy College of Engineering and Technology  Department of Humanities and Sciences  Hyderabad  501504  India,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Research and Development Center  Dubai Electricity and Water Authority (DEWA)"" 
        ""Kg Reddy College of Engineering and Technology""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Hyderabad""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""United Arab Emirates"" 
        ""India""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
        ""Department of Humanities and Sciences"" 
        ""501504""
    ]
}"
Baloch A.A.B.; Albadwawi O.; Alshehhi B.; Parida B.; Alberts V.,Balancing Aesthetics and Performance of Colored Perovskite-Silicon Tandem Solar Cells Through Simulation-Assisted Design,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183462788&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374473&partnerID=40&md5=60f0e973a35cd38491b5df0b40af9e56,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Research and Development Center  Dubai Electricity and Water Authority (DEWA)  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Research and Development Center""  ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority""  ""DEWA""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [""Dubai""] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Ali S.; Giachino M.; Bonani A.; Aprato A.; Riyahi-Alam S.; Khattab A.; Bignardi C.; Massè A.,Pelvic ring fractures: External fixation comparative numerical structural analysis,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923165904&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020934&partnerID=40&md5=abd5dc088471f342b1caa4c3908dca9d,1Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Mechanical Design and Production Engineering Department  Faculty of Engineering  Cairo University  Giza  Egypt; Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering Department  Politecnico di Torino  Torino  Italy; School of Medicine  University of Turin  Torino  Italy; Orthopaedic Department  School of Medicine  Orbassano  Italy,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Mechanical Design and Production Engineering Department""  ""Faculty of Engineering""  ""Cairo University""  ""Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering Department""  ""Politecnico di Torino""  ""School of Medicine""  ""University of Turin""  ""Orthopaedic Department""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Giza""  ""Torino""  ""Turin""  ""Orbassano""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""  ""Italy""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Seddik Z.B.; Smouh S.; Ahachad M.; Mahdaoui M.,Year-Round Performance Analysis of PV and PV-TEC Systems Under Different Climate Conditions,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183460928&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374534&partnerID=40&md5=b985ec1bea91c921dea7793e3cec3416,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,ETTE  Tangier  University of Abdelmalek Essaadi  Faculty of Sciences and Techniques  Morocco; Amee  The Moroccan Agency for Energy Efficiency  Morocco,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of Abdelmalek Essaadi"" 
    ""Faculty of Sciences and Techniques"" 
    ""The Moroccan Agency for Energy Efficiency""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""ETTE"" 
    ""Tangier"" 
    ""Amee""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Morocco"" 
    ""Morocco""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Michalikova M.; Abed R.; Prauzek M.; Koziorek J.,Image reconstruction in electrical impedance tomography using neural network,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923204634&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020959&partnerID=40&md5=8dab36af443078ccf3a9aacee9ba8b69,23Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,VSB - Technical University of Ostrava  Department of Cybernetics and Biomedical Engineering  Ostrava  Czech Republic; National School of Engineering of Tunis  Electrical Engineering Department  Tunis  Tunisia,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""VSB - Technical University of Ostrava""  ""Department of Cybernetics and Biomedical Engineering"" ""National School of Engineering of Tunis""  ""Electrical Engineering Department""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Ostrava""  ""Tunis""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Czech Republic""  ""Tunisia""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
nan,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183598230&partnerID=40&md5=b2e2946ee146e599feef703b22bcacf2,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,nan,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Sawaftah M.; Alshanqiti H.; Najeeb N.S.; Kumar S.; John J.J.; Mathiak G.; Alberts V.,Dust and Sand Analysis in Solar Parks,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183466230&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374523&partnerID=40&md5=5b9f1ef16a3caa944ca01fd58fcf1bcd,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dewa R&d Center  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Dewa R&D Center""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Dubai""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Stenchikov G.; Mostamandi S.; Shevchenko I.; Ukhov A.; Osipov S.,Coarse Dust Soiling and Fine Dust Dimming Effects on PV Panels Over the Arabian Peninsula,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183464172&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374528&partnerID=40&md5=59f4d323aa08b39e20fa88a6f003cedf,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,King Abdullah University of Science and Technology  Makkah Province  Thuwal  23955-6900  Saudi Arabia,-1,"{
	""ORGANIZATION"": [""King Abdullah University of Science and Technology""] 
	""LOCATION"": [""Makkah Province""  ""Thuwal""] 
	""COUNTRY"": [""Saudi Arabia""] 
	""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""23955-6900""]
}"
Zhu M.; Ayers M.; Dortland G.,Field Applications of PV Solar Systems on Landfills,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183465007&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374535&partnerID=40&md5=36b9b4f77885e3e86d963d9bf70885d9,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Watershed Geosynthetics  Alpharetta  30022  GA  United States; WatershedGeo Eu  Oldenzaal  Netherlands,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Watershed Geosynthetics"" 
    ""WatershedGeo Eu""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Alpharetta"" 
    ""Oldenzaal""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United States"" 
    ""Netherlands""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""30022"" 
    ""GA""
  ]
}"
Adothu B.; Kumar S.; Sreekuttan S.; Shekason Z.F.; Alheloo A.; Almheiri A.; John J.J.; Mathiak G.; Jaeckel B.; Gottschalg R.; Alberts V.,Discoloration Effect on Performance of PV Modules Installed in Middle East Hot Desert,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183460597&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374527&partnerID=40&md5=e5f7d0f8bd2046d856a11fdd8904473f,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dewa Research & Development Center  P.O.Box: 564  Dubai  United Arab Emirates; Fraunhofer Center for Silicon Photovoltaics Csp  Otto-Eissfeldt-Str. 12  Halle (Saale)  06120  Germany,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Dewa Research & Development Center"" 
        ""Fraunhofer Center for Silicon Photovoltaics Csp""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Halle (Saale)""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Germany""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
        ""P.O.Box: 564"" 
        ""Dubai"" 
        ""United Arab Emirates"" 
        ""Otto-Eissfeldt-Str. 12"" 
        ""06120""
    ]
}"
Parida B.; Najar A.; Baloch A.A.B.; Alshehhi B.; Albadwawi O.; Alberts V.,Plasmonic Au@SnO2 Core-Shell Hybrid Electron Transport Layer for Highly Efficient Planar Perovskite Solar Cells,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183464318&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374475&partnerID=40&md5=83ee355194b3ede92e00c4a4a2cb187c,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Research and Development Center  Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  Dubai  United Arab Emirates; College of Science  United Arab Emirates University  Department of Physics  Al Ain  15551  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Research and Development Center"" 
    ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority"" 
    ""College of Science"" 
    ""United Arab Emirates University"" 
    ""Department of Physics""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Al Ain""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""15551""
  ]
}"
Haider U.; Trepci E.; Rodriguez-Ubinas E.,Assessment of Photovoltaics Shading Devices (PVSD) Impact on the Energy Generation  Cooling Load  and Daylighting in an Office Building in Dubai,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183467305&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374491&partnerID=40&md5=9d7cb9b87bf2f608b13d29e307784a28,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Heriot-Watt University  United Kingdom; Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  Dewa R&d Centre  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Heriot-Watt University""  ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority""  ""Dewa R&d Centre""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Dubai""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Kingdom""  ""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Miaji Y.; Miaji M.,The Sunny Intelligence: A Novel Proposal for Combining the AI with Solar Power for Excellent Output Power Forcasting,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183460235&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374508&partnerID=40&md5=c347139ea7bb3b459b53682cfa80f707,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Technical and Vocational Training Corporation  Makkah  Jeddah  Saudi Arabia,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Technical and Vocational Training Corporation""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Makkah""  ""Jeddah""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Saudi Arabia""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Alzubaidi F.; Zhang D.; Tabet N.,Enhancing the Performance of Perovskite Solar Cells Through Antioxidant Incorporation,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183463869&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374539&partnerID=40&md5=df97c6d82e3eebc3959c5692e0f81f99,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Center for Advanced Materials Research (CAMR)  Research Institute of Sciences and Engineering (RISE)  University of Sharjah  P.O. Box 27272  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates; University of Sharjah  Department of Sustainable and Renewable Energy Engineering  P.O. Box 27272  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates; University of Sharjah  Department of Applied Physics & Astronomy  P.O. Box 27272  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Center for Advanced Materials Research"" 
    ""Research Institute of Sciences and Engineering"" 
    ""University of Sharjah"" 
    ""Department of Sustainable and Renewable Energy Engineering"" 
    ""Department of Applied Physics & Astronomy""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Sharjah""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""P.O. Box 27272""
  ]
}"
Ahmed N.K.; Wahed M.A.; Wahba K.K.,Reducing Laboratory Total Turnaround Time (TAT) using system dynamics simulation: Chemistry analyzer application,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923206928&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020927&partnerID=40&md5=27fe114a647438bdfcced36d5b86979e,2Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Systems and Biomedical Engineering Dept.  Faculty of Engineering  Cairo University  Giza  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Systems and Biomedical Engineering Dept."" 
    ""Faculty of Engineering"" 
    ""Cairo University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Giza""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Egypt""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Mathiak G.; Seentakath A.; Muthusamy A.; John J.J.,PV Module Cleaning Under Hot Desert Conditions: Creating Test Standards for PV Module Cleaning,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183467150&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374529&partnerID=40&md5=5524738847b493763eebae505cae4049,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dewa R&d Center  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Dewa R&d Center""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Dubai""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Gharieb R.R.; Gendy G.,Fuzzy C-means with a local membership kl distance for medical image segmentation,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923170015&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020912&partnerID=40&md5=c9cae414319dc81ed97fa7501e372505,19Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Department of Electrical Engineering  Assiut University  Assiut  71516  Egypt; El-Rajhy Liver Hospital  Assiut University  Assiut  Egypt,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Department of Electrical Engineering"" 
        ""Assiut University"" 
        ""El-Rajhy Liver Hospital"" 
        ""Assiut University""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Assiut""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Egypt""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
        ""71516""
    ]
}"
Irshad S.; Akram M.U.,Classification of retinal vessels into arteries and veins for detection of hypertensive retinopathy,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923170013&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020937&partnerID=40&md5=4d9850b05300db3be529327bf0c40ae5,38Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Department of Electrical Engineering  College of e and Me  National University of Sciences and Technology  Rawalpindi  Pakistan; Department of Computer Engineering  College of e and Me  National University of Sciences and Technology  Rawalpindi  Pakistan,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Department of Electrical Engineering"" 
    ""College of e and Me"" 
    ""National University of Sciences and Technology"" 
    ""Department of Computer Engineering""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Rawalpindi""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Pakistan""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Mathew L.E.; Panchal A.K.,Global Peak Detection with Novel PV Curve Triangle for Partially Shaded PV Modules,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183469177&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374488&partnerID=40&md5=3298739e5132553b97e1a7ed346659c2,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Sardar Vallabhbhai National Institute of Technology  Gujarat  Surat  395007  India,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Sardar Vallabhbhai National Institute of Technology""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Gujarat"" 
        ""Surat""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""India""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
        ""395007""
    ]
}"
Chapaneri K.; Aly S.P.; John J.J.; Mathiak G.,Tracking the Sun: Performance Analysis of Single-Axis vs Dual-Axis Solar PV Systems in UAE Desert Climate,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183466009&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374532&partnerID=40&md5=5fe1eefc1a83bc81b8122f451592a0fa,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Research and Development Center  Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Research and Development Center"" 
    ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Dubai""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Selim M.; Al-Shatouri M.; Kudo H.; Rashed E.A.,Compressed-sensing-based three-dimensional image reconstruction algorithm for C-arm vascular imaging,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923165888&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020930&partnerID=40&md5=09d875399c657a883225bfa6776721a5,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Math. and Computer Science Dept.  Faculty of Science  Suez University  Suez  Egypt; Radiology Dept.  Faculty of Medicine  Suez Canal University  Ismailia  Egypt; Computer Science Dept.  University of Tsukuba  Tsukuba  Japan; Image Science Lab.  Math. Dept.  Faculty of Science  Suez Canal University  Ismailia  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Math. and Computer Science Dept."" 
    ""Faculty of Science"" 
    ""Suez University"" 
    ""Radiology Dept."" 
    ""Faculty of Medicine"" 
    ""Suez Canal University"" 
    ""Computer Science Dept."" 
    ""University of Tsukuba"" 
    ""Image Science Lab."" 
    ""Math. Dept.""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Suez"" 
    ""Ismailia"" 
    ""Tsukuba""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Egypt"" 
    ""Japan""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Nayfeh L.; Nayfeh L.; Nayfeh A.,Solar Panel Roof Top Study and Optimization in Abu Dhabi  United Arab Emirates,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183461597&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374493&partnerID=40&md5=c23347781e6c6cf2347db776a414baf5,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dunecrest American School  Dubai  United Arab Emirates; Khalifa University  Abu Dhabi  127788  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Dunecrest American School"" 
    ""Khalifa University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Abu Dhabi""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""127788""
  ]
}"
Hamidi M.; Raihani A.; Bouattane O.; Al-Olama S.S.,Analyzing Microgrid Energy Profile Behavior to Study a Shared Energy Management System Based on AI: Dubai buildings Case Study,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183467733&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374504&partnerID=40&md5=3eed535e2c91929b8eb0989ad0915009,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Hassan Ii University of Casablanca  Electrical Engineering and Intelligent Systems Laboratory of Enset  Morocco; Energy and Petroleum Affairs in the Ministry of Energy and Infrastructure (MOEI)  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Hassan Ii University of Casablanca"" 
    ""Electrical Engineering and Intelligent Systems Laboratory of Enset"" 
    ""Ministry of Energy and Infrastructure (MOEI)""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Dubai""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Morocco"" 
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""Energy and Petroleum Affairs""
  ]
}"
Shahin M.K.,Wireless communication and RFID based handheld database and medical diagnostic system,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923177992&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020922&partnerID=40&md5=e3f274de05a369332b081a45bbb50cad,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Electrical Engineering Department  Faculty of Engineering  Suez Canal University  Ismailia  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Electrical Engineering Department""  ""Faculty of Engineering""  ""Suez Canal University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Ismailia""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Hassan S.A.; Sayed M.S.; Farag F.,Segmentation of breast cancer lesion in digitized mammogram images,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923169209&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020928&partnerID=40&md5=7627fc07163e2c0b44ba9dce82364105,9Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dept. of Electronics and Communications Engineering  Zagazig University  Zagazig  Egypt; Dept. of Electronics and Communications Engineering  Egypt-Japan University of Science and Technology  New Borg EI-Arab City  Alexandria  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Dept. of Electronics and Communications Engineering"" 
    ""Zagazig University"" 
    ""Egypt-Japan University of Science and Technology""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Zagazig"" 
    ""New Borg El-Arab City"" 
    ""Alexandria""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Egypt""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
El-Mohandes M.S.; El-Hussien Ibrahem M.,Stiffness analyses of modified niagara prosthetic feet using finite element modelling,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923205543&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020953&partnerID=40&md5=5d13e0b35488c3ddec3d8dcee75b0be7,6Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Systems and Biomedical Engineering Department  Higher Institute of Engineering  El-Shorouk City  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Systems and Biomedical Engineering Department""  ""Higher Institute of Engineering""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""El-Shorouk City""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Zeng T.; Ma J.; Dong M.,Environmental noise elimination of heart sound based on singular spectrum analysis,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923170046&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020943&partnerID=40&md5=afb2ea99d137423d02e4c082b1a67878,1Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering  Faculty of Science and Technology  University of Macau  Macao,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering"" 
    ""Faculty of Science and Technology"" 
    ""University of Macau""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Macau""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Abo-Zahhad M.; Ahmed S.M.; Abbas S.N.,A new biometric modality for human authentication using eye blinking,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923167026&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020949&partnerID=40&md5=63c2aa18cffc3591a1464f70f670f5cd,5Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering  Faculty of Engineering  Assiut University  Assiut  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering"" 
    ""Faculty of Engineering"" 
    ""Assiut University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Assiut""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Egypt""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Al Neyadi S.; Al Kuwaiti M.; Al Daheri S.; Al Marzroei M.; Al Ketbi A.; Alnajjar F.,Optimization of Large-Scale Solar Panels Distribution Using Genetic Algorithm,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183472647&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374524&partnerID=40&md5=b86966110ea0b1e11a87c307e80af85e,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,College of Information Technology (CIT)  Uae University  AlAin  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""College of Information Technology (CIT)""  ""Uae University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""AlAin""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Saad M.N.; Mabrouk M.S.; Eldeib A.M.; Shaker O.G.,Vitamin D receptor gene polymorphisms in rheumatoid arthritis patients associating osteoporosis,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923191742&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020919&partnerID=40&md5=6d2fee0972086264b535add7054c1343,7Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Biomedical Engineering Department  MUST 6th of October  Egypt; Systems and Biomedical Engineering Department  Cairo University  Giza  Egypt; Medical Biochemistry and Molecular  Biology Department  Cairo University  Cairo  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Biomedical Engineering Department"" 
    ""MUST"" 
    ""Systems and Biomedical Engineering Department"" 
    ""Cairo University"" 
    ""Medical Biochemistry and Molecular Biology Department""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""6th of October"" 
    ""Giza"" 
    ""Cairo""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Egypt""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Guler N.; Bayhan S.,MPPT-Based Model Predictive Control for Split Source PV Inverters,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183466493&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374505&partnerID=40&md5=129c065cbd3c5f7dc5df96f5f8c5d4cb,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Gazi University  Technology Faculty  Department of Electrical-Electronic Engineering  Ankara  Turkey; Qatar Environment and Energy Research Institute  Hamad Bin Khalifa University  Doha  Qatar,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Gazi University"" 
        ""Technology Faculty"" 
        ""Department of Electrical-Electronic Engineering"" 
        ""Qatar Environment and Energy Research Institute"" 
        ""Hamad Bin Khalifa University""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Ankara"" 
        ""Doha""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Turkey"" 
        ""Qatar""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Elramady M.M.; Sayed A.M.; Awadalla M.A.; Mohamed F.S.; Nassef T.M.,Measuring primary stability for the inclined implants retaining mandibular overdenture using resonance frequency,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923204335&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020923&partnerID=40&md5=cb7c0b5d4818d9c0c3c91dc063066f23,4Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Department of Prosthodontics  Alexandria University  Alexandria City  Egypt; Biomedical Engineering Department  Misr University for Science and Technology  6th of October City  Giza  Egypt; Computer and Software Department  Misr University for Science and Technology  6th of October City  Giza  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Department of Prosthodontics"" 
    ""Alexandria University"" 
    ""Biomedical Engineering Department"" 
    ""Misr University for Science and Technology"" 
    ""Computer and Software Department"" 
    ""Misr University for Science and Technology""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Alexandria City"" 
    ""6th of October City"" 
    ""Giza""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Egypt""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Al-Mansoori M.; Rezk A.; Askar K.; Nayfeh A.,MoS2 Nano Particles for UV Absorption in Solar Cells,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183470909&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374516&partnerID=40&md5=27f42c1ab0e333e8399a56fb30162ee9,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Khalifa University  Abu Dhabi  127788  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Khalifa University""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Abu Dhabi""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""United Arab Emirates""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
        ""127788""
    ]
}"
Abdulla H.; Sleptchenko A.; Nayfeh A.,Optimal Cleaning Schedule for Photovoltaic Fleet: Analyzing the Impact of Operational Costs on System Profitability,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183469763&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374514&partnerID=40&md5=4b1d87f7739b9311169527fea2586890,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Khalifa University  Department of Management Science and Engineering  Abu Dhabi  127788  United Arab Emirates; Khalifa University  Department of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science  Abu Dhabi  127788  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Khalifa University"" 
        ""Department of Management Science and Engineering"" 
        ""Department of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Abu Dhabi""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""United Arab Emirates""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
        ""127788""
    ]
}"
Alhamadani H.; Kumar S.; Mathiak G.; Alberts V.,Enhanced Defect Detection in Desert-Exposed PV Modules Through Three Imaging Techniques,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183462311&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374513&partnerID=40&md5=637633acc5f1a936c81d89ab7c3dea72,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Research & Develoment Center  Dubai Electricity & Water Authority (DEWA)  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Research & Develoment Center"" 
    ""Dubai Electricity & Water Authority (DEWA)""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Dubai""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Ramahi O.M.,Space-Based Solar Power: Addressing Fundamental Challenges towards Practical Implementation,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183469629&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374466&partnerID=40&md5=ecb57912edbece73ed5c60ab91e5415a,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Waterloo  Waterloo  N2L 3G1  ON  Canada,-1,"```json
{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": ""University of Waterloo"" 
    ""LOCATION"": ""Waterloo"" 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
        ""N2L 3G1""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": ""Canada""
}
```"
Eghbali A.; Ikonen E.; Karha P.,Differential Spectral Responsivity of Solar Cells Measured with an LED Based Experimental Setup,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183465423&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374492&partnerID=40&md5=774663da3a5e0974bbfb38b5cf9eeb57,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Metrology Research Institute  Aalto University  Espoo  02150  Finland; Vtt Mikes  Espoo  02150  Finland,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Metrology Research Institute""  ""Aalto University""  ""Vtt Mikes""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Espoo""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Finland""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""02150""]
}"
Al-Thani H.A.; Hasoon F.S.,Comprehensive Investigation on the Effect of Mo Back Contact Microstructural Properties on the CIGS Thin Film Microstructural Properties and Device Performance,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183461468&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374541&partnerID=40&md5=002eb9a86ed7c9a05e5f4bd258d69d5b,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,National Energy and Water Research Center (NEWRC)  P.O. Box 54111  Abu Dhabi  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""National Energy and Water Research Center""  ""NEWRC""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Abu Dhabi""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""P.O. Box 54111""]
}"
Zaka A.; Alhassan S.; Nayfeh A.,RF-Powered Sputtering of Iron Pyrite for Photovoltaic Applications,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183471702&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374540&partnerID=40&md5=7c1da1beb9796772cb23f389fadba74f,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Khalifa University  Abu Dhabi  127788  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Khalifa University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Abu Dhabi""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""127788""]
}"
Ali T.A.; Alzarooni K.; Alzarooni M.,Solar Resource Management Towards 100% Renewable Electricity,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183461228&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374474&partnerID=40&md5=c4545f06f3c570de9977aa865208c047,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dubai Electricity and Water Authority (DEWA)  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority""  ""DEWA""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Dubai""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Mohamed A.Z.; Eun S.; Lee J.; Park K.; Metwally M.K.; Kim T.-S.; Lee E.; Lee S.M.; Lee H.-J.; Lee S.; Choi W.,Unilateral facial nerve paralysis induced changes in DMN functional connectivity; A fMRI study,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923182933&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020913&partnerID=40&md5=6dcc6f523f3d3af4eda2a9128befa2cb,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Biomedical Engineering Deptart  Kyung Hee University  Youngin  South Korea; Korea Institute of Oriental Medicine (KIOM)  Daejeon  South Korea; Department of Acupuncture and Moxibustion  School of Oriental Medicine  Kyunghee University  Seoul  South Korea; Department of Radiology  Kyunghee University  South Korea,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Biomedical Engineering Deptart"" 
    ""Kyung Hee University"" 
    ""Korea Institute of Oriental Medicine (KIOM)"" 
    ""School of Oriental Medicine"" 
    ""Department of Radiology""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Youngin"" 
    ""Daejeon"" 
    ""Seoul""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""South Korea""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Alkhalid A.; Baha A.; Sasidharan A.; Louis J.D.; Abbas M.; Uyoh N.; Francis W.-E.O.,Illuminating Possibilities: A Comprehensive Review of Concentrating Solar Technologies for Sustainable Energy Solutions,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183457542&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374519&partnerID=40&md5=9790f1728799e8accb7701c9daccf5b8,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Cranfield University  Bedfordshire  Cranfield  MK43 0AL  United Kingdom,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Cranfield University""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [""Bedfordshire""  ""Cranfield""] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""United Kingdom""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""MK43 0AL""]
}"
Burgert O.; Fink E.; Wiemuth M.; Thies C.,A model-guided peri-operative information systems approach,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923197059&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020926&partnerID=40&md5=9f75b3f05bbc423651f4f7641fb0f385,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Research Group Computer Assisted Medicine (CaMed)  Dept. of Informatics  Reutlingen University  Reutlingen  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Research Group Computer Assisted Medicine (CaMed)""  ""Dept. of Informatics""  ""Reutlingen University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Reutlingen""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Germany""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Riad M.,Assessment of Cooling Effectiveness in Power Yields of a Multi-Orientational BIPV Façade of a High-Rise Building in a Hot and Arid Region: The Octagonal Tower,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183473567&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374490&partnerID=40&md5=c7d0e6a08125f5e99a2074777df2e7b5,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Mrfs Power Building Contracting  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": ""Mrfs Power Building Contracting"" 
  ""LOCATION"": ""Dubai"" 
  ""COUNTRY"": ""United Arab Emirates"" 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": """"
}"
Zaccari I.; Davies A.G.; Walti C.; Laurenson S.X.,Label-free electrochemical biosensors for clinical diagnostic,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923205930&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020946&partnerID=40&md5=63f59a820492bfce99c7a0b409ce2a9b,6Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Leeds  School of Electronic and Electrical Engineering  Woodhouse Lane  Leeds  LS2 9JT  United Kingdom; Abbott GmbH and Co  Max Planck Ring 2  Wiesbaden  65205  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of Leeds"" 
    ""School of Electronic and Electrical Engineering"" 
    ""Abbott GmbH and Co""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Woodhouse Lane"" 
    ""Leeds"" 
    ""Max Planck Ring 2"" 
    ""Wiesbaden""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Kingdom"" 
    ""Germany""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""LS2 9JT"" 
    ""65205""
  ]
}"
Aly S.P.; Chapaneri K.; John J.J.; Mathiak G.; Alarm M.A.,Retrofitting the Translation Equations of the One-Diode Model for Photovoltaic Modules,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183474019&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374515&partnerID=40&md5=a07a08f3f5d01a5aa21f4cd128a12965,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Research and Development Center  Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  Dubai  United Arab Emirates; Purdue University  Electrical and Computer Engineering Department  West Lafayette  IN  United States,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Research and Development Center"" 
        ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority"" 
        ""Purdue University"" 
        ""Electrical and Computer Engineering Department""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Dubai"" 
        ""West Lafayette""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""United Arab Emirates"" 
        ""United States""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Nader A.; Eldeib A.M.,A novel approach for remote diagnosis and troubleshooting for lab instruments,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923167310&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020910&partnerID=40&md5=ecbe8b7466c81925d589ad7525e89a77,1Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Systems and Biomedical Engineering Department  Faculty of Engineering  Cairo University  Giza  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Systems and Biomedical Engineering Department""  ""Faculty of Engineering""  ""Cairo University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Giza""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Guillermo J.E.; Sanchez E.N.; Ricalde L.J.; Cruz B.J.; Castillo A.,Intelligent classification of real heart diseases based on radial wavelet neural network,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923174477&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020944&partnerID=40&md5=945c5e057514c1b95ebe90b5db39e59f,3Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,CINVESTAV of IPN  Automatic Control Department  Mailbox 31-438  Guadalajara Jalisco  C.P. 44550  Mexico; UADY  Faculty of Engineering  Av. Industrias No Contaminantes Por Periferico Norte  Apdo. Postal 115  Cordemex  Merida  Yucatan  Mexico,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""CINVESTAV of IPN""  ""UADY  Faculty of Engineering""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Automatic Control Department""  ""Mailbox 31-438""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Mexico""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""Guadalajara Jalisco""  ""C.P. 44550""  ""Av. Industrias No Contaminantes Por Periferico Norte""  ""Apdo. Postal 115""  ""Cordemex""  ""Merida""  ""Yucatan""]
}"
Alheloo A.; Almheiri A.; Kumar S.; Mathiak G.; Alberts V.,Characterization and Analysis of PV Module Defects and Degradation Mechanisms through Use of Module External Quantum Efficiency,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183465553&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374500&partnerID=40&md5=8af4d54ef6b6e699e889519d7085d341,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dubai Electricity and Water Authority (DEWA) R&d Center  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority (DEWA) R&d Center"" 
    ""LOCATION"": ""Dubai"" 
    ""COUNTRY"": ""United Arab Emirates"" 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": """"
}"
Elazab A.; Hu Q.; Jia F.; Zhang X.,Content based modified reaction-diffusion equation for modeling tumor growth of low grade glioma,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923165945&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020929&partnerID=40&md5=db4201a5de5ffe28f5b8642a303e6b57,9Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Research Lab for Medical Imaging and Digital Surgery  Shenzhen Institutes of Advanced Technology  University Town of Shenzhen  1068 Xueyuan Boulevard  Xili Nanshan  518055  China; Shenzhen College of Advanced Technology  University of Chinese Academy of Sciences  Shenzhen  China; Faculty of Computers and Informations  Masnoura University  Mansoura city  Egypt,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Research Lab for Medical Imaging and Digital Surgery"" 
        ""Shenzhen Institutes of Advanced Technology"" 
        ""University College of Advanced Technology"" 
        ""University of Chinese Academy of Sciences"" 
        ""Faculty of Computers and Informations"" 
        ""Masnoura University""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""University Town of Shenzhen"" 
        ""1068 Xueyuan Boulevard"" 
        ""Xili Nanshan"" 
        ""Mansoura city""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""China"" 
        ""China"" 
        ""Egypt""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Matharani K.; Jariwala H.,Washout Filter-Based Droop Control for Solar PV Based Microgrid,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183458242&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374499&partnerID=40&md5=ebe1a8942f919d401f370b8f812c105d,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Svnit  Electrical Engineering Department  Surat  India,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Svnit""  ""Electrical Engineering Department""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [""Surat""] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""India""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Alkhalidi A.; Boretti A.; Owhaib W.; Salameh T.; Hader M.; Al-Kouz W.,Design of a Solar CSP Plant for Ma'an  Jordan,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183465610&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374497&partnerID=40&md5=d5f91f00a483bedbdbea7e6b75a7d648,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Sharjah  Sustainable and Renewable  Engineering Department  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates; Jordan University of Science and Technology  Aeronautical Engineering Department  Irbid  Jordan; German Jordanian University  Mechanical and Maintenance Engineering Department  Amman  Jordan; University of North Alabama  Department of Engineering and Industrial Professions  Florence  35632  AL  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Sharjah""  ""Jordan University of Science and Technology""  ""German Jordanian University""  ""University of North Alabama""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Sharjah""  ""Irbid""  ""Amman""  ""Florence""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""  ""Jordan""  ""Jordan""  ""United States""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""Sustainable and Renewable""  ""Engineering Department""  ""Aeronautical Engineering Department""  ""Mechanical and Maintenance Engineering Department""  ""Department of Engineering and Industrial Professions""  ""35632""  ""AL""]
}"
Sugimoto H.,Feasibility Study of Rechargeable Flexible Tandem Solar Cells for VIPV Applications Under Realistic Environments,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183460202&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374538&partnerID=40&md5=5307805172ea2b97d2e07ea10ee77d0d,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Pxp Corporation  Kanagawa  Sagamihara  252-0131  Japan,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Pxp Corporation""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Kanagawa"" 
        ""Sagamihara"" 
        ""252-0131""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Japan""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Kabra R.,Reliability Availability and Maintainability Study for Concentrated Solar Plants and How to Account for Current Limitations and Challenges,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183461932&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374501&partnerID=40&md5=bda7b3c1d71e713562f090ede6a31134,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Risktec Solutions Dmcc  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Risktec Solutions Dmcc""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Dubai""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Alhammadi N.; Alantali M.; Rodriguez-Ubinas E.,Crystalline Silicon Solar PV Integration in Residential Buildings: Case Studies From Solar Decathlon Middle East,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183464889&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374543&partnerID=40&md5=60923ee61ed3e808cbd13b611dae0962,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  Dewa R&d Centre  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority"" 
    ""Dewa R&d Centre""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Dubai""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Riad M.; Chapaneri K.; Rodriguez-Ubinas E.; John J.J.; Mathiak G.,Temperature and Energy Yield Study of Façade Building Integrated PV Modules in Hot Desert Region,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183470643&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374494&partnerID=40&md5=eb1b09df92bf924484f66405b254d2a3,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Research and Development Center  Dewa  Dubai  United Arab Emirates; Mrfs Power Building Contracting  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Research and Development Center""  ""Mrfs Power Building Contracting""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Dubai""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""Dewa""]
}"
Dehghani S.; Daon U.; Shariatzadeh M.,Propelling a Paradigm Shift: Revolutionizing Energy Yield in Solar Photovoltaic Systems,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183471059&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374472&partnerID=40&md5=2886bc77278299d78813372909755b52,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Daanaa Resolution Inc.  Vancouver  V6A lA4  BC  Canada,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Daanaa Resolution Inc.""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Vancouver""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Canada""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""V6A lA4"" 
    ""BC""
  ]
}"
Saleh N.; Rosati S.; Sharawi A.; Wahed M.A.; Balestra G.,Application of quality function deployment and genetic algorithm for replacement of medical equipment,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923169186&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020925&partnerID=40&md5=5218b65bf880feaf8a82b8d95133773b,6Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Biomedical Engineering Department  Faculty of Engineering  Cairo University  Giza  Egypt; Electronics and Telecommunication Department  Politecnico di Torino  Torino  Italy,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Biomedical Engineering Department""  ""Faculty of Engineering""  ""Cairo University""  ""Electronics and Telecommunication Department""  ""Politecnico di Torino""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Giza""  ""Torino""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""  ""Italy""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Gostein M.; Stueve B.,Applications of In-Situ Module I-V Measurement for PV System Performance Monitoring & Control,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183473873&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374463&partnerID=40&md5=f8ec2207b63f1226fd5fa785dcb96818,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Atonometrics  Austin  78757  TX  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Atonometrics""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Austin""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""78757"" 
    ""TX""
  ]
}"
Irshad S.; Salman M.; Akram M.U.; Yasin U.,Automated detection of Cotton Wool Spots for the diagnosis of Hypertensive Retinopathy,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923197783&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020932&partnerID=40&md5=3520c16466fd777362d4e237013ca8ef,18Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Department of Electrical Engineering  College of e and Me  National University of Sciences and Technology  Rawalpindi  Pakistan; Department of Computer Engineering  College of e and Me  National University of Sciences and Technology  Rawalpindi  Pakistan; Department of Ophthalmology  Armed Forces Institute of Ophthalmology  Rawalpindi  Pakistan,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Department of Electrical Engineering"" 
        ""College of e and Me"" 
        ""National University of Sciences and Technology"" 
        ""Department of Computer Engineering"" 
        ""Department of Ophthalmology"" 
        ""Armed Forces Institute of Ophthalmology""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Rawalpindi""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Pakistan""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Seddik N.; Youssef S.; Kholief M.,Automatic seizure detection in long-term scalp EEG using Weighted Permutation Entropy and Support Vector Machine,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923169223&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020948&partnerID=40&md5=4fb8e788f21e42f5b5c2ee42827f5901,2Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Computer Department-College of Engineering  Arab Academy for Science and Technology (AAST)  Alexandria  Egypt; College of Computer Science and Information Technology  Arab Academy for Science and Technology (AAST)  Alexandria  Egypt,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Computer Department-College of Engineering  Arab Academy for Science and Technology (AAST)"" 
        ""College of Computer Science and Information Technology  Arab Academy for Science and Technology (AAST)""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Alexandria""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Egypt""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Elsayed M.; El-Sherry T.; Abdelgawad M.,Development of Computer Assisted Sperm Analysis (CASA) plugin for analyzing sperm in microfluidic environments using Image-J,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923171956&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020941&partnerID=40&md5=1467c54af5cb6ba26609b16857017017,4Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Assiut University  Assiut  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Assiut University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Assiut""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Abdellah M.; Eldeib A.; Sharawi A.,Offline large scale fourier volume rendering on low-end hardware,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923171958&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020915&partnerID=40&md5=2fde4eb4546b58f0f840e720e91a7263,4Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Systems and Biomedical Engineering Department  Cairo University  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Systems and Biomedical Engineering Department""  ""Cairo University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Egypt""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Makram A.W.; Khalifa A.M.; El-Wakad M.T.; El-Rewaidy H.; Fahmy A.S.; Ibrahim E.-S.H.,Evaluation of cardiac left ventricular mass from Tagged Magnetic Resonance Imaging,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923171959&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020917&partnerID=40&md5=7377dc0832fcffd0c3533e847edc214f,2Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Biomedical Engineering Department  Helwan University  Cairo  Egypt; Biomedical Engineering Department  Cairo University  Cairo  Egypt; University of Michigan Ann Arbor  MI  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Biomedical Engineering Department"" 
    ""Helwan University"" 
    ""Cairo University"" 
    ""University of Michigan""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Ann Arbor""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Egypt"" 
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""MI""
  ]
}"
Alzahmi W.; Alyaarbi A.; Alnaqbi T.; Alzaatreh A.,Performance Analysis of Building Integrated Photovoltaic (BIPV): MANOVA Analysis,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183464114&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374542&partnerID=40&md5=1326b4ad3f999d2dca5bb9c372bc17fa,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  Dubai  United Arab Emirates; American University of Sharjah  Sharjah  Department of Industrial Engineering  Engineering Systems Management Program  Sharjah  26666  United Arab Emirates; College of Arts and Sciences  American University of Sharjah  Sharjah  Department of Mathematics and Statistics  Sharjah  26666  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority"" 
    ""American University of Sharjah"" 
    ""Department of Industrial Engineering"" 
    ""Engineering Systems Management Program"" 
    ""College of Arts and Sciences"" 
    ""Department of Mathematics and Statistics""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Dubai"" 
    ""Sharjah""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""26666""
  ]
}"
Qureshi A.N.,A framework for segmentation and estimation of intracranial measurements in CT scans,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923166807&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020936&partnerID=40&md5=91c0d4b7a8d759b1e037d250aeb29a16,1Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Bedfordshire  United Kingdom,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of Bedfordshire""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Kingdom""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Manandhar P.; Rafiq H.; Kumar S.; Qureshi O.A.; Rodriguez-Ubinas E.,Identification of Micro-Defects in Solar Cells using Electroluminescence Images via Hybrid Approach,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183466815&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374502&partnerID=40&md5=79e0cbe3513ebea43863ccb8b486e094,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dewa R&d Centre  Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  P.O. Box 564  Dubai  564  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Dewa R&d Centre"" 
    ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Dubai""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""P.O. Box 564"" 
    ""564""
  ]
}"
Mousa M.A.; Almansoori A.N.; Alajami F.A.,A Hybrid PV Power Forecasting Model Implementing Emerging Machine Learning Algorithms: Prophet and Neural Prophet,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183457281&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374512&partnerID=40&md5=adf070aa80b17623f2ffa661e85e6061,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Rochester Institute of Technology  Department of Graduate Programs and Research  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Rochester Institute of Technology"" 
    ""Department of Graduate Programs and Research""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Dubai""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Alami A.H.; Ayoub M.; Alashkar A.; Alasad S.; Mdallal A.; Khuri S.; Aljaghoub H.,Photoresponse of Thermally Evaporated Copper Oxide-Based Solar Cells,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183465966&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374521&partnerID=40&md5=5102d135eb61db8329560a0fb938b974,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Sharjah  Sustainable Energy & Power Systems Research Centre  Sustainable and Renewable Energy  Engineering Department  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates; American University of Sharjah  Materials Science and Engineering PhD Program  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates; American University of Sharjah  Mechancial Engineering Department  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates; University of Sharjah  Sustainable Energy & Power Systems  Research Centre  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates; University of Sharjah  Industrial Engineering and Engineering  Management Department  Sharjah  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""University of Sharjah"" 
    ""Sustainable Energy & Power Systems Research Centre"" 
    ""Engineering Department"" 
    ""American University of Sharjah"" 
    ""Materials Science and Engineering PhD Program"" 
    ""Mechanical Engineering Department"" 
    ""Industrial Engineering and Engineering Management Department""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Sharjah""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""Sustainable and Renewable Energy""
  ]
}"
Roshen W.,Load Independent  Enhanced Power Extraction from a Solar Cell: Modifying the Output Characteristics of a Solar Cell Externally,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183462857&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374471&partnerID=40&md5=eb416170bc008358f413c140e4b8b5d1,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Ss Power Technology  Hilliard  43026  OH  United States; The Ohio State University  Columbus  43210  OH  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Ss Power Technology"" 
    ""The Ohio State University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Hilliard"" 
    ""Columbus""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""43026"" 
    ""43210"" 
    ""OH""
  ]
}"
Kalaghichi S.S.; Preis P.; Lossen J.; Hob J.; Werner J.H.,Progress in TOPCon Cell Development and Laser Process for the Integration of Front Side Passivated Contacts,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183458895&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374507&partnerID=40&md5=392af806187206c005d83d501d1c6e8c,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,International Solar Energy Research Center Konstanz  Konstanz  78467  Germany; Institute for Photovoltaics  University of Stuttgart  Stuttgart  70569  Germany,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""International Solar Energy Research Center Konstanz""  ""Institute for Photovoltaics  University of Stuttgart""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [""Konstanz""  ""Stuttgart""] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""Germany""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""78467""  ""70569""]
}"
Hassanein A.S.; Khalifa A.M.; El-Wakad M.T.,Estimation of Eulerian strain from tagged MRI using Optical flow,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923165958&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020916&partnerID=40&md5=ef00d228e677853b003aff5b9c4164ae,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Biomedical Engineering Department  Helwan University  Cairo  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Biomedical Engineering Department""  ""Helwan University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Cairo""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Mousa D.; Zayed N.; Yassine I.A.,Automatic cardiac MRI localization method,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923171662&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020942&partnerID=40&md5=c67513e123a08038270271b61fdd0002,5Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Computers and Systems  Electronic Research Institute  Giza  Egypt; Systems and Biomedical Engineering  Cairo University  Giza  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Electronic Research Institute"" 
    ""Cairo University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Giza  Egypt""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""Computers and Systems"" 
    ""Systems and Biomedical Engineering""
  ]
}"
Makary M.M.; Bu-Omer H.M.; Kadah Y.M.,Spectral subtraction denoising improves accuracy of Slow Cortical Potential based brain-computer interfacing,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923197674&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020947&partnerID=40&md5=546d3be6d89e2515db5cd409a2c511b7,2Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Systems and Biomedical Engineering  Cairo University  Giza  Egypt; Electrical and Computer Engineering  King Abdul Aziz University  Jeddah  Saudi Arabia,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Systems and Biomedical Engineering  Cairo University"" 
        ""Electrical and Computer Engineering  King Abdul Aziz University""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Giza"" 
        ""Jeddah""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Egypt"" 
        ""Saudi Arabia""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Ahmed O.; Abdellah H.; Elsayed M.; Abdelgawad M.; Mousa N.A.; El-Badri N.,Tissue dissociation miniaturized platform for uterine stem cell isolation and culture,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923197794&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020950&partnerID=40&md5=089f014761814fd31af6ec2c929b6229,3Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Faculty of Medicine  Assiut University  Assiut  Egypt; Mechanical Engineering Department  Assiut University  Assiut  Egypt; Center of Excellence of Stem Cells and Regenerative Medicine  Zewail City of Science and Technology  Cairo  Egypt,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Faculty of Medicine  Assiut University""  ""Mechanical Engineering Department  Assiut University""  ""Center of Excellence of Stem Cells and Regenerative Medicine  Zewail City of Science and Technology""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [""Assiut""  ""Cairo""] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Mathiak G.; John J.J.; Najeeb N.S.; Alshanqiti H.; Sawaftah M.; Seentakath A.; Kumar S.; Gabbadi P.; Kumar Y.; Alberts V.; Mirza M.,PV Modules Sand and Brush Abrasion Testing,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183463034&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374465&partnerID=40&md5=bfaa4f7bc06661680ff59a2f4b4a2d5e,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dewa R&d Center  Dubai  United Arab Emirates; Fraunhofer Isc  Würzburg  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Dewa R&d Center""  ""Fraunhofer Isc""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Dubai""  ""Würzburg""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""  ""Germany""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Mohamad C.; Jean S.,Survey of Machine Learning-Based Predictions of Photovoltaic Power Outputs,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183460583&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374517&partnerID=40&md5=9bce1d7502558686ffd8658dff999943,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dar Al Handasah- Shair & Partner  Beirut  Lebanon,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": ""Dar Al Handasah- Shair & Partner"" 
  ""LOCATION"": ""Beirut"" 
  ""COUNTRY"": ""Lebanon""
}"
Dalibor T.; Stolzel M.; Elanzeery H.; Aboulfadl H.; Eraerds P.; Borowski P.; Reichel R.; Didschuns I.; Frankenberger H.,World Record Efficiency Cd-Free CIGS Modules and Their Advances for Large-Scale Production,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183464301&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374518&partnerID=40&md5=7bc605212bd80ae9d81589791c70c4b9,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Avancis GmbH  Bavaria  Munich  81739  Germany; Avancis GmbH  Saxony  Torgau  04860  Germany,-1,"```json
{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Avancis GmbH""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Bavaria"" 
    ""Munich"" 
    ""Saxony"" 
    ""Torgau""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Germany""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""81739"" 
    ""04860""
  ]
}
```"
Salman Y.M.; El-Dakhakhni W.W.; Mekky W.,Development of a high resolution human brain finite element model for restructuring Traumatic Brain Injury,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923165843&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020911&partnerID=40&md5=02095fa8a791e952fbe1caa526089bb7,2Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dep. of Research and Development  Egyptian Armed Forces  Cairo  Egypt; Dep. of Biomedical Engineering  McMaster University  Hamilton  Canada; Dep. of Stress Analysis  AMEC NSS  Toronto  Canada,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Dep. of Research and Development  Egyptian Armed Forces"" 
        ""Dep. of Biomedical Engineering  McMaster University"" 
        ""Dep. of Stress Analysis  AMEC NSS""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Cairo"" 
        ""Hamilton"" 
        ""Toronto""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Egypt"" 
        ""Canada""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Dellimore K.; Smith J.; Scheffer C.,The influence of ventilation on chest compression force and depth during neonatal cardiopulmonary resuscitation,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923184887&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020955&partnerID=40&md5=9349f731cf880445ec825fed5e76c3c6,1Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Biomedical Engineering Research Group  Department of Mechanical and Mechatronic Engineering  Stellenbosch University  South Africa; Department of Paediatrics and Child Health  Tygerberg Hospital and Stellenbosch University  South Africa,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Biomedical Engineering Research Group"" 
    ""Department of Mechanical and Mechatronic Engineering"" 
    ""Stellenbosch University"" 
    ""Department of Paediatrics and Child Health"" 
    ""Tygerberg Hospital""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""South Africa""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Al-Sabounchi A.; Alnuaimi M.; Ashaar M.; Jaber M.; Al-Qdaimat M.; Ghodayah A.,Harmonic Emissions Assessment of Distributed Photovoltaic Systems in Low Voltage Network,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183461676&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374537&partnerID=40&md5=469b0362ded9bff254bda19a2d41d480,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Power and Water Planning  Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Power and Water Planning""  ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Dubai""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Mboup A.; Akisawa A.,Comparison of the Truncation Effect on the Newly Designed Multi-Profile 3D Solar Concentrators and the Conventional 3D Compound Parabolic Concentrator,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183471753&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374489&partnerID=40&md5=d05a158cc68ee58955e52fbb42882703,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Tokyo University of Agriculture and Technology  Koganei  Tokyo  184-8588  Japan,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Tokyo University of Agriculture and Technology""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Koganei""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Japan""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
        ""184-8588""
    ]
}"
Alam F.; El-Atab N.,3D Printing of Zinc Oxide Nanoparticles Embedded Transparent Sheet for Solar Panel Encapsulation and Thermal Management,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183463858&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374495&partnerID=40&md5=4d5ef9389dc5ced5f705b9e2665e9f36,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,King Abdullah University of Science and Technology (KAUST)  Electrical and Computer Engineering  Computer Electrical Mathematical Science and Engineering Division  Thuwal  23955-6900  Saudi Arabia,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""King Abdullah University of Science and Technology"" 
        ""Electrical and Computer Engineering"" 
        ""Computer Electrical Mathematical Science and Engineering Division""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Thuwal""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""Saudi Arabia""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
        ""23955-6900""
    ]
}"
Haider U.; Qureshi O.A.; Shahzad A.A.; Bozdar Baloch A.A.; Rodriguez-Ubinas E.,Assessment of PV Performance-Enhancing Technologies in Desert Climate Conditions of Dubai,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183470266&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374531&partnerID=40&md5=d10d84bd2c14a9f8c6d1d907f4e3ce14,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Heriot-Watt University  Dubai  United Arab Emirates; Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  Dewa R&d Centre  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Heriot-Watt University"" 
    ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority"" 
    ""Dewa R&d Centre""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Dubai""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Subramani A.; Senthil C.; Sarkar K.J.; Sofer Z.,Electric Field Simulation of Ultrathin CuInP2S6 Solar Cells,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183458421&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374496&partnerID=40&md5=b6829e006f0d066d0a2dc867577bb7d7,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,University of Chemistry and Technology Prague  Department of Inorganic Chemistry  Czech Republic; Gyeongsang National University  Department of Energy Engineering  South Korea,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [""University of Chemistry and Technology Prague""  ""Department of Inorganic Chemistry""  ""Gyeongsang National University""  ""Department of Energy Engineering""] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [""Czech Republic""  ""South Korea""] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Manandhar P.; Alzarouni S.; Trepci E.; Rafiq H.; Rodriguez-Ubinas E.,Impacts of Photovoltaic Modules on Residential Buildings in Dubai,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183461719&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374520&partnerID=40&md5=072554023c8524f42dfeb1647394f3a7,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dewa R&d Centre  Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  P.O. Box 564  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Dewa R&d Centre""  ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Dubai""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""P.O. Box 564""]
}"
Alshaiba K.,Active Liquid Based Thermal Management of PV Modules,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183468592&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374509&partnerID=40&md5=1bc3e1f57343f9f41f05ca3dac777cb8,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dewa  Middle East  Dubai  United Arab Emirates; Transmission Power  Transmission Maintenance Department  Transmission Civil Maintenance  Electro Machanical  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Dewa""  ""Transmission Power""  ""Transmission Maintenance Department""  ""Transmission Civil Maintenance""  ""Electro Machanical""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Middle East""  ""Dubai""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Kumar S.; Adothu B.; John J.J.; Mathiak G.; Jackel B.; Gottschalg R.; Alberts V.,Enhancing Durability of PV Modules in MENA Region: The Hot Desert Test Protocol,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183457604&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374498&partnerID=40&md5=9d5bf3e92feb6700f0dbc25c64ab0237,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Dewa Research & Development Center  P.O.Box: 564  Dubai  United Arab Emirates; Fraunhofer Center for Silicon Photovoltaics Csp  Otto-Eissfeldt-Str. 12  Halle (Saale)  06120  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Dewa Research & Development Center""  ""Fraunhofer Center for Silicon Photovoltaics Csp""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Halle (Saale)""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""  ""Germany""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""P.O.Box: 564""  ""Otto-Eissfeldt-Str. 12""  ""06120""]
}"
Alzahmi W.; Ndiaye M.,AHP Decision-Making Approach for Solar Photovoltaic (PV) Modules End-Of-Life (EOL) Disposition Strategies,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183473656&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374487&partnerID=40&md5=8a3eb22029d8be5432cfd1810689b108,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,American University of Sharjah  Sharjah  Sharjah  26666  United Arab Emirates; American University of Sharjah  Engineering Systems Management Program  Department of Industrial Engineering  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""American University of Sharjah"" 
    ""Engineering Systems Management Program"" 
    ""Department of Industrial Engineering""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Sharjah""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""United Arab Emirates""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""26666""
  ]
}"
Hassanein A.M.D.E.,A slab to reduce back-reflected clutter for the whole Ultra-WideBand range,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923194810&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020918&partnerID=40&md5=10310901832bbe04e55203d498e38445,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Systems and Information Dept  Engineering Division  National Research Centre  Dokki  Cairo  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""National Research Centre""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Dokki  Cairo""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""Systems and Information Dept""  ""Engineering Division""]
}"
Cyrus M.; Bruce A.; Frolov S.; Moussouris J.,PV-Plus: High-Performance  Multi-Functional Skins for UAV,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183463189&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374530&partnerID=40&md5=aad64f2ebb3065ec9632ce80786bf4d3,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Sunlight Aerospace Inc.  Colorado  81069  United States,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Sunlight Aerospace Inc.""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Colorado""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United States""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [""81069""]
}"
Majid Ali Al Risi A.R.; Khamis Al-Zaabi F.H.; Salim Al Washahi A.M.; Mohammed Al-Maaini R.K.; Boddu M.K.,Advancing Solar PV Component Inspection: Early Defect Detection with UAV Based Thermal Imaging and Machine Learning,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183463101&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374464&partnerID=40&md5=ada91d2e11abc3e0fa3567f87d11fc96,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,College of Engineering & Technology  University of Technology & Applied Sciences-Shinas  Engineering Department  PO Box 324 Al Aqr  Oman,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""College of Engineering & Technology"" 
    ""University of Technology & Applied Sciences-Shinas"" 
    ""Engineering Department""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Al Aqr""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Oman""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""PO Box 324""
  ]
}"
Obaid S.; Alhamadani H.; Alyammahi M.; Mathiak G.,Optical Properties of 3D-Printed Solar Panel Front Cover Using Clear Resin,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183469048&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374462&partnerID=40&md5=0171a35ad927648492e90996958c3d1f,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Research & Development Center  Dubai Electricity & Water Authority (DEWA)  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Research & Development Center"" 
        ""Dubai Electricity & Water Authority"" 
        ""DEWA""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Dubai""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""United Arab Emirates""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Rezk M.; Chikte R.; Aljasmi N.; Baloch A.A.B.,PV Module Classification Based on Spatial Distribution of Soiling Using Deep Learning Model,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183465226&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374510&partnerID=40&md5=2ed809107e2a9b578c60b56a9c46ab71,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Research and Development Centre Dubai Electricity and Water Authority  Dubai  United Arab Emirates,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Research and Development Centre""  ""Dubai Electricity and Water Authority""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Dubai""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""United Arab Emirates""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
El-Sherry T.M.; Elsayed M.; Abdelhafez H.K.; Abdelgawad M.,Characterization of rheotaxis of bull sperm using microfluidics,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923169536&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020951&partnerID=40&md5=6fce33a5126cf809e4ac70fa3e4b460e,1Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Assiut University  Assiut  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Assiut University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Assiut""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Nazif K.N.; Nitta F.U.; Daus A.; Saraswat K.C.; Pop E.,Performance Limits of Transition Metal Dichalcogenide Solar Cells,2023 Middle East and North Africa Solar Conference  MENA-SC 2023 - Proceedings,2023,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-85183467093&doi=10.1109%2fMENA-SC54044.2023.10374533&partnerID=40&md5=a0fdd5c1e417f5002243e6d38f795708,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Stanford University  Stanford  94305  CA  United States; Rwth Aachen University  Aachen  52074  Germany,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Stanford University"" 
    ""Rwth Aachen University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Stanford"" 
    ""Aachen""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Germany"" 
    ""United States""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""94305"" 
    ""CA"" 
    ""52074""
  ]
}"
Sheha M.A.; Sharwy A.; Mabrouk M.S.,Pigmented skin lesion diagnosis using geometric and chromatic features,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923171967&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020931&partnerID=40&md5=563b25a6f7062f41275f4e3a7135be44,9Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Biomedical and System Engineering  Cairo University  Giza  Egypt; Biomedical Engineering Dept.  MUST University  6 of October  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Cairo University"" 
    ""MUST University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Giza"" 
    ""6 of October""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Egypt"" 
    ""Egypt""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": [
    ""Biomedical and System Engineering"" 
    ""Biomedical Engineering Dept.""
  ]
}"
Hamdi M.M.; Awad M.I.; Abdelhameed M.M.; Tolbah F.A.,Lower limb motion tracking using IMU sensor network,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923164191&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020957&partnerID=40&md5=fb519af327fe2fdec1a40633bad1f228,18Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Mechatronics Department  Ain Shams University  Cairo  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Mechatronics Department""  ""Ain Shams University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Cairo""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Abdelfadeel M.A.; Elshehaby S.; Abougabal M.S.,Automatic segmentation of left ventricle in cardiac MRI using Maximally Stable Extremal Regions,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923136575&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020940&partnerID=40&md5=7e7fc52f4e1761bfb467ed78c03eaf95,5Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Biomedical Engineering Department  Medical Research Institute  Alexandria University  Alexandria  Egypt; Computer and Systems Engineering Department  Faculty of Engineering  Alexandria University  Alexandria  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Biomedical Engineering Department"" 
    ""Medical Research Institute"" 
    ""Alexandria University"" 
    ""Computer and Systems Engineering Department"" 
    ""Faculty of Engineering""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Alexandria""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Egypt""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
nan,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923372858&partnerID=40&md5=310a05fb84496022e81ae7fc4af45bf5,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,nan,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [] 
    ""LOCATION"": [] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Prauzek M.; Hlavica J.; Michalikova M.; Jirka J.,Fuzzy clustering method for large metabolic data set by statistical approach,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923163240&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020924&partnerID=40&md5=add450f7e02738f1bd37600b0b57028c,3Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,VSB - Technical University of Ostrava  Department of Cybernetics and Biomedical Engineering  Ostrava  Czech Republic,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""VSB - Technical University of Ostrava"" 
    ""Department of Cybernetics and Biomedical Engineering""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Ostrava""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Czech Republic""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Abdellah M.; Eldeib A.; Sharawi A.,MATLAB-based fourier volume rendering framework,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923130980&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020914&partnerID=40&md5=88532cc837d50d476dc282a52fdb838a,3Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Systems and Biomedical Engineering Department  Cairo University  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": ""Systems and Biomedical Engineering Department  Cairo University"" 
  ""LOCATION"": ""Cairo"" 
  ""COUNTRY"": ""Egypt"" 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": """"
}"
Elson W.; Scheffer C.; Dellimore K.H.; Fourie P.R.; Coetzee A.R.,Development of an intravenous oxygenator using microbubbles,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923138737&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020920&partnerID=40&md5=5892af9cc2210992f04217faa336dc8b,0Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Department of Mechanical and Mechatronic Engineering  Stellenbosch University  South Africa; Department of Anaesthesiology and Critical Care  Faculty of Health Sciences  University of Stellenbosch  South Africa,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Department of Mechanical and Mechatronic Engineering"" 
    ""Stellenbosch University"" 
    ""Department of Anaesthesiology and Critical Care"" 
    ""Faculty of Health Sciences"" 
    ""University of Stellenbosch""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Stellenbosch""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""South Africa""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Shaker M.S.; Wael M.; Yassine I.A.; Fahmy A.S.,Cardiac MRI view classification using autoencoder,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923120013&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020935&partnerID=40&md5=c2be24abdda4715ba0ca916aa15eff40,5Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Center for Informatics Science  Nile University  Giza  Egypt; Diagnosoft Inc  Cairo  Egypt; Systems and Biomedical Engineering  Cairo University  Giza  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [""Center for Informatics Science""  ""Nile University""  ""Diagnosoft Inc""  ""Systems and Biomedical Engineering""  ""Cairo University""] 
  ""LOCATION"": [""Giza""  ""Cairo""] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [""Egypt""] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Eldeeb S.M.; Fahmy A.S.,Error analysis of fundus image registration using quadratic model transfformation,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923165836&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020938&partnerID=40&md5=b1546afcf167d4f07a0de4a664dec6c2,1Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Center for Informatics Science  Nile University  Cairo  Egypt; Systems and Biomedical Engineering Dept.  Cairo University  Cairo  Egypt,-1,"{
  ""ORGANIZATION"": [
    ""Center for Informatics Science"" 
    ""Nile University"" 
    ""Systems and Biomedical Engineering Dept."" 
    ""Cairo University""
  ] 
  ""LOCATION"": [
    ""Cairo""
  ] 
  ""COUNTRY"": [
    ""Egypt""
  ] 
  ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
Metwally M.K.; El-Gohary S.H.; Han S.M.; Byun K.M.; Kim T.-S.,Influence of the anisotropic mechanical properties of the breast cancer on photoacoustic imaging,Proceedings of the 7th Cairo International Biomedical Engineering Conference  CIBEC 2014,2015,https://www.scopus.com/inward/record.uri?eid=2-s2.0-84923164208&doi=10.1109%2fCIBEC.2014.7020958&partnerID=40&md5=2a4c7ad66969f55ddc69020a5f352242,6Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Inc.,Department of Biomedical Engineering  Kyung Hee University  Yongin  Gyeonggi  South Korea,-1,"{
    ""ORGANIZATION"": [
        ""Department of Biomedical Engineering"" 
        ""Kyung Hee University""
    ] 
    ""LOCATION"": [
        ""Yongin"" 
        ""Gyeonggi""
    ] 
    ""COUNTRY"": [
        ""South Korea""
    ] 
    ""MISCELLANEOUS"": []
}"
